<GSP VER="3.2">
	<TM>0.685812</TM>
	<Q>marathon</Q>
	<PARAM name="entqr" value="0" original_value="0"/>
	<PARAM name="access" value="p" original_value="p"/>
	<PARAM name="getfields" value="\*" original_value="\*"/>
	<PARAM name="output" value="xml_no_dtd" original_value="xml_no_dtd"/>
	<PARAM name="sort" value="date:D:L:d1" original_value="date%3AD%3AL%3Ad1"/>
	<PARAM name="ie" value="UTF-8" original_value="UTF-8"/>
	<PARAM name="btnG" value="Google Search" original_value="Google\+Search"/>
	<PARAM name="client" value="active_frontend" original_value="active_frontend"/>
	<PARAM name="q" value="marathon" original_value="marathon"/>
	<PARAM name="ud" value="1" original_value="1"/>
	<PARAM name="site" value="active_collection" original_value="active_collection"/>
	<PARAM name="oe" value="UTF-8" original_value="UTF-8"/>
	<PARAM name="ip" value="98.224.243.12" original_value="98.224.243.12"/>
	<RES SN="1" EN="10">
		<M>141000</M>
		<FI/>
		<NB>
			<NU>/search?q=marathon&amp;site=active_collection&amp;hl=en&amp;lr=&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;output=xml_no_dtd&amp;client=active_frontend&amp;access=p&amp;sort=date:D:L:d1&amp;getfields=*&amp;start=10&amp;sa=N</NU>
		</NB>
		<R N="1">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Can_using_sport_balms_replace_a_good_warm-up_on_the_bike_.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Can_using_sport_balms_replace_a_good_warm-up_on_the_bike_.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Can_using_sport_balms_replace_a_good_warm-up_on_the_bike_.htm</UD>
			<T>Can using sport balms replace a good warm-up on the bike?</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="For years, cyclists have used alagesic sport rubs like Ben Gay to warm-up, especially before cold weather rides. Is it a substitue for a good warm-up? Dr Ed Burke has the answer."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=39054"/>
			<S>Stand in the staging area of any bicycle race on a cold and damp day and you will smell the aroma of menthol in the air. The source of the scent is a tube of Musculor, Cramergesic, Ben-Gay, Icy Hot or one of the dozens of other products on the market. &lt;p&gt;

Technically known as analgesics or counterirritants, they have become a part of pre-race preparation for the cyclist. Their use in cycling is strictly to aid in "warm-up" or as a source for relief for muscle soreness. &lt;p&gt;

They are known as counterirritants because they produce a slight irritation of the skin and therefore create a sensation of warmth ranging from mild to intense. As we will see later the heat that builds up in the leg muscles is a result of the massaging action of the trainer or by the pre-race riding is greater than that caused by the use of the analgesic itself. &lt;p&gt;

Analgesics are made in varying strengths. The perceived strength of a particular analgesic is dependent up on the sensitivity of the skin on which it is applied. Putting a mild analgesic such as Icy-Hot on one cyclist will produce a particular sensation. The sensation may not be the same on a cyclist whose skin is not as sensitive. &lt;p&gt;

Also, a cyclist would not use a "hot" counterirritant such as Red Hot on both their thigh muscles and neck, because these areas have different sensitivities and will react differently. &lt;p&gt;

The most popular ingredient in analgesics is methyl salicylate, found in wintergreen oil or else prepared synthetically. When put on your legs, it causes the skin to turn red and produces a feeling of warmth. Methyl salicylate is safe when used no more than three or four times per day. But a cyclist, who is sensitive to aspirin, should monitor the use of methyl salicylate since it is related to aspirin. &lt;p&gt;

Menthol is the second-most widely used ingredient in counterirritants and is produced synthetically or extracted from peppermint oil. Menthol stimulates the nerves that perceive cold while depressing those that perceive pain. The immediate effect is a sense of coolness, followed by sensations of warmth. &lt;p&gt;

With this combination of menthol and methyl salicylate a mixed sensation of cold and warmth is sent to the brain, which diminishes the perception of pain. Which is why these products are used after a hard effort when you experience soreness in your muscles. The fragrance of the menthol also acts psychologically to take your mind off your sore muscles. &lt;p&gt;

Whether or not these products aid in warming-up is a question that has been raised for many years. Studies conducted at the University of California, at San Diego measured the effect of rubbing Ben-Gay on the legs as an aid in warming-up before strenuous exercise. &lt;p&gt;

Two groups of runners were used the studies. One group warmed-up and applied Ben-Gay to their legs. The other group warmed-up without Ben-Gay. The runners then engaged in a prolonged treadmill run. The runners recorded the amount of discomfort they were encountering at various times during the run. The runners who warmed-up with Ben-Gay ran with significantly greater comfort for a longer period of time. &lt;p&gt;

The researcher concluded that Ben-Gay is an effective aid to warm-up and that proper warm-up with Ben-Gay can help one exercise more comfortably for longer periods of time. &lt;p&gt;

While the results of this study are significant, one should not forget that a proper warm-up on the bike is important to good performance. The sensation of warmth produced by the analgesic may make some cyclists think they are ready for racing when, in fact, their muscles may be too tight for all-out exertion.  &lt;p&gt;

In cool, damp weather a product with an oil or Vaseline type base will also help keep the rain off your legs and block the wind. It is wise to have a coach or masseur apply the product to your legs since it is not wise to start the race with these products on your hands. If you rub your eyes or lips you'll soon learn not to apply them yourself. &lt;p&gt;

Rubbing alcohol and an old towel are the best cleaning agents to get an analgesic balm off your hands or to clean off your legs after the race. &lt;p&gt;

Never apply analgesics to bruised or abraded skin, since absorption into the body can produce unwanted effects. If a rash develops, stop using the product and try another one. Finally, avoid using counterirritants near sensitive areas as lips, eyes and crotch area. &lt;p&gt;

In addition to the legs in cold weather do not forget to roll up your cycling shorts to get the upper thigh and roll down your socks in order to get the Achilles tendon. It is also wise to apply some to the lower back if it is sore and arms if you are wearing a short sleeve jersey. &lt;p&gt;

So, while counterirritants will add in warm-up and help you recover from muscle soreness, they are not a replacement for a good warm-up on the bicycle. &lt;p&gt;

Warming up prepares the entire body for the hard effort of racing. It prepares the cardiovascular system by gradually increasing the demand on the body's systems so that when the race starts (such as a hill climb) it can be better accommodated by the cardiovascular system. With the musculoskeletal system, a proper warm-up increases metabolism in preparation for faster and more forceful muscle movements. &lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Online training diary. Use our&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.active.com/activetrainer/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Active trainer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;b&gt;to record your mileage and vital stats.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt; 

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Shop for cycling gear and much more at the&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.activesportsmecca.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Active Sports Mecca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;a href="/advanced_search.cfm" align=center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Find and register for a bike tour or race in your area!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;


&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Got a question for Dr. Burke? &lt;a href="mailto:mark@racegate.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Send it here.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="2">
			<U>http://www.active.com/fitness/Articles/Spring_sports_injury_prevention.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/fitness/Articles/Spring_sports_injury_prevention.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/fitness/Articles/Spring_sports_injury_prevention.htm</UD>
			<T>Spring sports injury prevention</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Injury prevention is one of the most most important parts of training for a team sports athlete. Every sport has its share of accompanying injuries, but as the saying goes, “You can’t help your team if you're in street clothes.&quot;"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Fitness"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=42977"/>
			<S>&lt;!--noad--&gt;
Injury prevention is one of the most most important parts of training for a team sports athlete. Every sport has its share of accompanying injuries, but as the saying goes, “You can’t help your team if you're in street clothes." This is why it's important to train, not only to build strength, but reduce the risk of injury.
&lt;p&gt;Injuries usually occur due to one of three following reasons: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="1" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lack       of conditioning&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Muscular       imbalances&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improper       development of dynamic joint range of motion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every injury can be prevented. But training programs structured to prevent injury, often called   pre-habilitation (pre-hab), make it easer (and less painful) to prevent an injury  from occurring in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are my favorite pre-hab exercises  for baseball, softball and soccer that will hopefully keep you on the field for most of the spring and summer. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead"&gt;Shoulder capsule pre-hab&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Internal  External Rotation:&lt;/strong&gt; With bands looped under the feet, and upper arm parallel to  the ground, rotate hands down so they are level with the elbow -- and then back up with  constant tension. Perform three sets of 12-15 reps two to three times per week. Light dumbbells  can be used.&lt;/li&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cuban  Press:&lt;/strong&gt; As above, hold bands at your side, pinch shoulders back and then pull  weight up, with constant tension, so that upper arm is parallel to ground. Perform three sets of 12-15 reps three times per week. Light dumbbells can  be  used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p class="subhead"&gt;Hip/lower body pre-hab&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set hurdles at  hip height and perform three to five sets of two of the exercises below per day -- with three to five  hurdles constituting a full set. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="1" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side movement, lead leg over:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand  right of        hurdles. Raise lead leg over, maintaining a slight bend in the leg.       Proceed to the next hurdle with a slight skip; be sure to stay on the       balls of your feet as you plant each leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ol start="2" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side movement, cross-over leg over:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand left of        hurdles. Raise your crossover leg over, maintaining a slight bend in       the leg. Proceed to the next hurdle with a slight skip, and stay on       the balls of your feet as you plant each leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ol start="3" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side movement, lead leg, then opposite:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand  right       of  hurdles. Raise  lead leg over (again, maintaining a slight       bend) and then off to the side. Proceed to the next hurdle with a slight       skip; stay on the balls of your feet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ol start="4" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front movement, from side: &lt;/strong&gt;Stand facing  hurdles. Proceed       with one leg at a time by raising each knee over the first hurdle. Proceed       to the next hurdle with a slight skip; stay on the balls of your feet as       you plant each leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;!--pagebreak--&gt;
&lt;!--noad--&gt;
&lt;ol start="5" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Front movement, down center:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand facing hurdles. Raise       lead leg over the first hurdle -- bring trail leg over       the second hurdle. (The hurdles must be set close enough to accommodate       this.) Stay on the balls of your feet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ol start="6" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duck under, stay low throughout:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand perpendicular to    hurdles. Duck under  first hurdle with  lead leg. Make sure movement is initiated by pushing buttocks back and that your feet face forward.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Stay in a low squat position throughout this drill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ol start="7" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duck under, pop up:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand perpendicular to hurdles. Duck       under the first hurdle with your lead leg. Make sure movement is       initiated by pushing  buttocks back and that your feet face forward.  Pop up from the squatting position after you clear each hurdle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ol start="8" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duck under, twist, stay low:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand perpendicular to the       hurdles. Duck under the first hurdle with your lead leg, and then twist to       lead under the second hurdle with your opposite leg. Make sure your       movement is initiated by pushing your buttocks back and that your feet       face forward.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Stay in a low squat position throughout the drill.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ol start="9" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duck under, twist, pop up:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand perpendicular to  hurdles.       Duck under first hurdle with  lead leg, and then twist to lead       under  second hurdle with opposite leg. Make sure your movement is       initiated by pushing your buttocks back and that your feet always face       forward. Pop up from the squatting position after you clear each hurdle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ol start="10" type="1"&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forward zig-zag duck under:&lt;/strong&gt; Stand facing  hurdles arranged in a zig-zag pattern. (Zig-zag: Each successive hurdle offset one       length from the previous hurdle.) Duck under each hurdle, and pop up       between them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A suggested daily work pattern for hurdle work is  as such: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Monday&lt;/strong&gt; -- movements  4 and 5 &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Tuesday &lt;/strong&gt;-- movements 1  and 2 &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday &lt;/strong&gt;-- movements 5 and  6 &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Thursday&lt;/strong&gt; -- movements 7  and 8 &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Friday&lt;/strong&gt; -- movements 9 and 10 &lt;/p&gt;
  Not only will this workout  bullet-proof your body, but it will make  you a better athlete as well. 
  &lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jon Doyle, MA, CSCS is an internationally published strength &amp;amp; conditioning specialist. His cutting-edge methods are used by professional athletes from all major sports, as well as youth sports participants from around the globe. For more information check out his new Web site
&lt;a href="http://aml.active.com/newsletter_redirect.jsp?U=15651&amp;M=$subst('recip.memberid')&amp;MS=$subst('outmail.messageid')" target="_blank"&gt; DoyleFitness.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="3">
			<U>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/The_Gear_Junkie__Holiday_Season_Gear.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/The_Gear_Junkie__Holiday_Season_Gear.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/The_Gear_Junkie__Holiday_Season_Gear.htm</UD>
			<T>The Gear Junkie: Holiday Season Gear</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Here's a quick look at eight Gear Junkie-approved items, all under $100, to consider for someone special on your list."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Gear"/>
			<MT N="tags" V=",,"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Features &amp; News"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=44579"/>
			<S>Of all seasons, the holidays are the easiest time of year to drop cash on gear and goodies for the great outdoors. Here's a quick look at eight Gear Junkie-approved items, all under $100, to consider for someone special on your list.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;SUGOi Subzero Skull Cap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This bike helmet-compatible beanie has a low drop in the back to cover your neck completely to the collar. A waterproof/breathable laminate finish eschews precipitation but lets your head still have air. $20, &lt;a href="http://www.sugoi.com" title="Sugoi" target="_blank"&gt;www.sugoi.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/BigAgnes_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Big Agnes Mountain Booty&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Big Agnes Mountain Booty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Technical slippers are a reality. If you've ever winter camped, you know the pain of cold feet in a tent or snow cave. These PrimaLoft-insulated booties have an ankle drawstring to cinch securely on your feet. They pack down small to become all but unnoticeable in a pack. $40, &lt;a href="http://www.bigagnes.com" title="Big Agnes" target="_blank"&gt;www.bigagnes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/KeenBag_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Keene Hawthorne Backpack&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Keen Hawthorne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Breed a backpack with a messenger bag and you get this unique shoulder "sling" bag, which sits secure with a single wide strap across your chest. It's made of recycled polyester and has a rubber bottom for durability and water resistance. Best for city bike trips, errands or tromping around town. $55, &lt;a href="http://www.keenfootwear.com" title="Keen" target="_blank"&gt;www.keenfootwear.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/PuffyQuilt_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;180s Puffy Quilt&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;180s Puffy Quilt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Insert stereo headphones into a cozy set of earmuffs and you have the Puffy Quilt, a behind-the-head design ear-warming unit compatible with MP3 players like the iPod. Its cord is removable for times when warmth is still needed, but your music is not. $40, &lt;a href="http://www.180s.com" title="180s" target="_blank"&gt;www.180s.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/LambGirl_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Shred Alert Lambgirl hat&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shred Alert Lambgirl&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yes, this is an acrylic/lambsuede cowboy hat made for winter sports. It has a bendable brim and a cozy, fuzzy interior to keep your noggin warm. Statement or style? You can decide. $48, &lt;a href="http://www.shredalert.com" title="Shred Alert" target="_blank"&gt;www.shredalert.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/Spork_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Spork XM&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Spork XM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The spork is a mainstay of camping culture. This update of an old design fashions the spork out of a durable polycarbonate that brings its weight down to a half-ounce. Its features include a spoon, fork tines and a small serrated knife-like edge. &lt;a href="http://www.light-my-fire.com" title="Light My Fire" target="_blank"&gt;www.light-my-fire.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/SurvivorPak_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;S.O.L. Survival Pak&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Adventure Medical Kits S.O.L. Survival Pak&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Made for wilderness survival in a time of emergency, you better pray your friend or family member never employs this gift. The S.O.L. Pak puts several survival items in an ultralight waterproof bag. In total, the 4.6-ounce kit includes a mirror; a whistle; matches; tinder; a space blanket; bilingual survival and first aid instructions; a fishing kit; duct tape; and a compass. $25, &lt;a href="http://www.adventuremedicalkits.com" title="Adventure Medical Kits" target="_blank"&gt;www.adventuremedicalkits.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style="padding-right: 5px; float: left;"&gt;&lt;img src="/Assets/Gear/TarmaEarrings_150x150.jpg" height="125" width="125" /&gt;&lt;div style="font-size: 8px; font-style: italic; font-weight: normal;"&gt;Tarma Designs Jewelry&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Tarma Designs Jewelry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The outdoors-themed jewelry in Tarma's line, most of which is made from recycled stainless steel, is designed for women and men, including pendants, bracelets and earrings. Most pieces are low-profile and can be worn during activities ranging from running to yoga. Prices start at $20, &lt;a href="http://www.tarmadesigns.com" title="Tarma Designs" target="_blank"&gt;www.tarmadesigns.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="4">
			<U>http://www.active.com/running/Articles/Top_1999_Age_Group_Performances_are_in.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/running/Articles/Top_1999_Age_Group_Performances_are_in.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/running/Articles/Top_1999_Age_Group_Performances_are_in.htm</UD>
			<T>Top 1999 Age Group Performances are in</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="5">
			<U>http://www.active.com/mountainbiking/Articles/Power_training_for_mountain_bikers.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/mountainbiking/Articles/Power_training_for_mountain_bikers.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/mountainbiking/Articles/Power_training_for_mountain_bikers.htm</UD>
			<T>Power training for mountain bikers</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Power meters are changing the way we train by recording accurate and specific information on which to base our training plan decisions. For mountain bikes, there are two options: Power-Tap or SRM."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Mountain Biking"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=40589"/>
			<S>Power meters are changing the way we train by recording accurate and specific information on which to base our training plan decisions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This impacts both the micro level -- how many watts to produce for a single interval -- and the macro level -- how much training stress to accumulate over the course of a season to reach your ultimate peak. Road cyclists are leading the charge on the power-training front but power information is still valid and applicable to mountain biking.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;There are currently only two reliable and accurate power meters available to fit a mountain bike. The least expensive is a Power-Tap. This requires a dedicated rear hub that is not disc compatible, so you have to go retro and run V-brakes. I love my disc brakes, so on my mountain bike I have the other option, an SRM. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SRM requires dedicated cranks. I have not taken any special precautions with my SRM and it has proven to be very durable off-road. The mountain bike SRM is a significant investment and one of the biggest reasons most mountain bikers are not taking advantage of the fantastic training information power meters provide. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are serious about your performance, a power meter is an advantage to have on your bike. So few mountain bikers have them it will be like your secret training weapon.&lt;/p&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="6">
			<U>http://www.active.com/soccer/Articles/David_Beckham_Welcomed_Into_MLS_22218.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/soccer/Articles/David_Beckham_Welcomed_Into_MLS_22218.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/soccer/Articles/David_Beckham_Welcomed_Into_MLS_22218.htm</UD>
			<T>David Beckham Welcomed Into MLS</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="LA Galaxy celebrated David Beckham's arrival with a dramatic reception. Will their expensive new player change the face of soccer in the U.S. like the MLS hopes?"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Soccer"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Features &amp; News"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=40520"/>
			<S>A tactic involves a decision followed by an action. There are two types of tactics; race tactics and preparative tactics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Race tactics are made on the fly during a race. Race tactics can be discussed and scenarios thought out but during a race you must act and react constantly to a changing situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preparative tactics are less elusive and can be organized, practiced and perfected during training.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Preparative tactics involve decisions and actions that you have control over. Preparative tactics include:&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;li&gt; Training taper &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Equipment choice &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Prerace rest and ride schedule &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Prerace meal &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Warm-up routine &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Selecting what gear to use on the starting line &lt;br&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Race nutrition and hydration strategy (knowing what and when you will eat and drink) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no excuses for making preparative tactical mistakes. Spending three hours inspecting the course the day before an event will take the snap out of your legs on race day -- and is a stupid tactical mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Racing with no water or sports drink leads to dehydration and a sub-optimal performance -- and is a preparative tactical mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don't put yourself in the position of saying "I knew better than to _____." Perfect your preparative race tactics until they are second nature and become a prerace ritual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Successfully repeating this prerace ritual gives you the confidence that you are perfectly prepared to race each time you toe the start line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;hr width="200" noshade&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lynda Wallenfels raced professionally as a cyclist garnering multiple championship titles. She currently specializes in coaching mountain bikers and Xterra triathletes and counts top 5 nationally ranked athletes among her current clientele. She is a certified coach through USA Cycling and USA Triathlon and can be reached at lwallenfels@ultrafit.com.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;a href="/advanced_search.cfm" align=center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Search Active and register online for an event in your area! &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="7">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Colorado_State_Patrol_ends_cap_on_cycling_events.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Colorado_State_Patrol_ends_cap_on_cycling_events.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Colorado_State_Patrol_ends_cap_on_cycling_events.htm</UD>
			<T>Colorado State Patrol ends cap on cycling events</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<S>DENVER -- During a press conference this afternoon the Colorado State Patrol is expected to announce the end of its policy capping the size of bicycle events previously set to begin December 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Removing the 2,500-person limit on bicycling events is the result of a cooperative effort between the State Patrol, the Colorado Department of Transportation, and Bicycle Colorado to implement best practices for event safety and access for all road users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--insertad--&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;"Bicycle events are important to the health and lifestyle of Colorado's citizens," confirms Dan Grunig, director of nonprofit Bicycle Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Our working group found that good planning, education, and enforcement have a tremendous influence on safety."&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;Colorado has many cycling events that draw more than 2,500 participants, attracting tourists to Colorado from all over the world, pumping millions into the state's economy. &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;The cooperative work group has also brought about the following bike-friendly outcomes:&lt;ul&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event safety&lt;/strong&gt; - Best practices identified to promote bicycling event safety&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unsafe driving hotline&lt;/strong&gt; - Cyclists who observe unsafe driving that endangers bicyclists can dial The State Patrol's CSP hotline to report aggressive driving.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cycling safety education&lt;/strong&gt; - Event directors are taking additional steps to promote bicycle safety education, including new training classes and roadside signs with safety tips and reminders &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safe roads&lt;/strong&gt; - Working together to proactively keep roads safe, including support for developing streets that are designed to be safe for &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; road users&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;
 
Bicyclists are pleased to have the State Patrol collaborating closely on bicycle safety. Their willingness to adopt an alternative to a cap on events shows their commitment to keeping rides safe and open for all. &lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Bicycle Colorado&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
Bicycle Colorado is a nonprofit organization dedicated to building a bicycle-friendly Colorado. They're supported by thousands of members who work together to protect the rights of bicyclists and improve bicycling conditions. &lt;a href="http://bicyclecolo.org/index.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;www.BicycleColorado.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="8">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Giro_d_Italia__Cipollini_sprints_for_fourth_stage_win__Simoni_is_overall_champion.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Giro_d_Italia__Cipollini_sprints_for_fourth_stage_win__Simoni_is_overall_champion.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Giro_d_Italia__Cipollini_sprints_for_fourth_stage_win__Simoni_is_overall_champion.htm</UD>
			<T>Giro d'Italia: Cipollini sprints for fourth stage win, Simoni is overall champion</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<S>MILAN, Italy (AP) - Gilberto Simoni won by a commanding lead his first Giro d'Italia title in one of the most-troubled, doping-tainted editions of the Italian cycling race.  &lt;p&gt;

Simoni, of the Lampre team, completed Sunday's last stage in the main group, retaining the pink jersey of overall leader and a seven-minute advantage over Spanish runnerup Abraham Olano.  &lt;p&gt;

Italy's ``king of sprints'' Mario Cipollini, of Saeco, eventually won the closing stage, edging Germany's Telekom team Danilo Hondo in a crowded finish in downtown Milan.  &lt;p&gt;

However, Simoni's crown will be forever clouded by a doping scandal in the final week of the race, which caused the cancellation of one stage, the expulsion of Simoni's top challenger Dario Frigo and spreading rumors that more doping suspensions may be looming.  &lt;p&gt;

``Let's wait before celebrating Simoni's victory,'' Rome's sports daily Corriere dello Sport wrote in a frontpage editorial comment on Sunday.  &lt;p&gt;

``Let's wait that results of anti-doping tests and of last Wednesday's police search are made public,'' Corriere added, calling the prestigious three-week Italian competition ``a black Giro.''.  &lt;p&gt;

A sweeping police raid in the hotels of 20 Giro teams at San Remo last Wednesday led to the seizure of reportedly banned substances and used syringes.  &lt;p&gt;

Investigators who decided the overnight raid by dozens of policemen were expected to announce details about the seized substances and possible indictments in the next few days.  &lt;p&gt;

The Italian state-run television network RAI alleged on Sunday that about 60 cyclists and team officials may be involved.  &lt;p&gt;

Under a recently enforced law, those taking or administering banned substances in sports can be convicted and sentenced up to three years in jail.  &lt;p&gt;

Simoni claimed that he was clean, and that his victory in this year's Giro, following a third-place finish in the previous, was the result of hard training.  &lt;p&gt;

``I'm clean, my conscience is clean. This victory is the happiest moment in my life,'' he said. ``I only got cheers along the course. I believe that in cycling there is a strong will to be clean and sincere.''  &lt;p&gt;

Simoni also said he may start in the French Tour next month. A final decision would be taken by the Giro winner next week.  &lt;p&gt;

The 29-year-old Italian cyclist, a good climber with a thin record in five years as a professional, clinched a single stage victory in the Giro, while holding the pink jersey in the last eight legs.  &lt;p&gt;

Simoni, who was born at Palu di Giovo - the same village near Trento of former Italian cycling great Francesco Moser - built up his huge lead in two tough mountainous stages at Passo Pordoi and Arona while fighting off Frigo's challenge in an individual time test at Salo, in the 15th stage.  &lt;p&gt;

Frigo, who trailed Simoni by only 15 seconds overall, was yanked by his Fassa Bortolo team before the start of Saturday's next-to-last leg after banned performance-enhancing substances were found in his hotel room during the police raid.  &lt;p&gt;

Police searches, which caused nationwide sensation while landing a blow to the fragile credibility of the sport, forced cancellation of Thursday's much-anticipated leg in the Alps as some riders had been kept awake into the early hours.  &lt;p&gt;

Last Wednesday, a French and an Italian cyclist were pulled out of the Giro by their teams after each tested ``non-negative'' in preliminary doping tests.  &lt;p&gt;

In a separate but still shocking case a few days earlier, one of the Giro favorites, Waldimir Belli, was ejected by the jury for punching and knocking down a fan who insulted him in the final kilometers of a 14th-stage climb.  &lt;p&gt;

Simoni's overall victory, the fifth consecutive by an Italian cyclist in the Giro, was achieved in absence of a tough challenge.  &lt;p&gt;

American Lance Armstrong did not enter the Italian race, to concentrate on his third consecutive Tour de France victory.  &lt;p&gt;

Olympic champion Jan Ullrich started in the 84th edition of the Giro with the declared goal to warmup for the French Tour, and ended one hour and 31 minutes behind the winner.  &lt;p&gt;

Marco Pantani, a Giro and Tour de France champion in 1998, withdrew during the final week, blaming an illness - and a questionable form. He had a gap of nearly 30 minutes.  &lt;p&gt;

Pantani was banned from the Giro that he was leading in 1999, after failing a blood test.  &lt;p&gt;

Last year's Giro winner Stefano Garzelli was knocked out by a bronchitis in the second week of the race.  &lt;p&gt;

Olano, of the Once team, never was a threat for Simoni overall as he trailed the Italian leader throughout and finished 7:31 minutes behind.  &lt;p&gt;

Another Spaniard, Unai Osa Eizaguirre, placed third in the final standings, nearly nine minutes behind.  &lt;p&gt;

Ivan Gotti, a two-time Giro winner, finished seventh and made headlines mostly for the police seizure of a number of medicines in the caravan of his father-in-law.  &lt;p&gt;

Gotti claimed the substances were intended to treat his allergies - yet another obscure case in a darkened race.  &lt;p&gt;

Sunday's last stage, the 20th of an original 21-leg program, was a sort of parade for Gilberto Simoni, who was cheered by the crowd along the course and complimented by his opponents.  &lt;p&gt;

Ullrich was among those who shook hands with Simoni, while pedaling toward Milan.  &lt;p&gt;

``Congratulations from my rivals especially pleased me,'' said Simoni who had a sleepless night on the eve of his first major career triumph.  &lt;p&gt;

Cipollini, 34, clinched his fourth stage win in this year's Giro with a powerful sprint on a wide stretch nearby the Sforza castle, following a 10-lap city circuit.  &lt;p&gt;

``SuperMario'' collected his 34th career stage win to move seven wins short of an all-time record of late Italian great Alfredo Binda.  &lt;p&gt;

Cipollini covered the 121-kilometer (75.02-mile) flat course from Arona to Milan in three hours, five minutes and one second.  &lt;p&gt;

Giro's director Carmine Castellano, while announcing that next year's Giro will start from the Netherlands, said the police raid in San Remo put the race at risk as most cyclists at one moment threatened a mass withdrawal.  &lt;p&gt;

``Luckily we managed to make it to Milan,'' Castellano said. &lt;p&gt;

&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Stage 21: Final results following the last stage of the Giro dItalia, 121K from Arona to Milan: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt;
1. Mario Cipollini, Italy, Saeco, three hours, five minutes, one second or 40.536 kph (25.132 mph).  &lt;br&gt;
2. Danilo Hondo, Germany, Telekom, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
3. Marco Zanotti, Italy, Liquigas, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
4. Mauro Gerosa, Italy, Tacconi Sport, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
5. Ivan Quaranta, Italy, Alexia, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
6. Stefano Casagranda, Italy, Alessio, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
7. Andrej Hauptmann, Slovenia, Tacconi Sport, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
8. Stefano Zanini, Italy, Mapei, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
9. Guido Trenti, United States, Cantina Tollo, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
10. Paolo Bossoni, Italy, Tacconi Sport, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
11. Massimo Strazzer, Italy, Mobilvetta, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
12. Davide Casarotto, Italy, Alessio, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
13. GiamPaolo Mondini, Italy, Mercatone Uno, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
14. Ief Verbrugghe, Belgium, Lotto, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
15. Martin Hvastja, Slovenia, Alessio, same time. &lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Selected riders:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

24. Abraham Olano, Spain, Once, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
25. Maximilian Sciandri, Britain, Lampre, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
31. Peter Luttenberger, Austria, Tacconi Sport, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
34. Unai Osa Eizaguirre, Spain, Banesto, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
41. Jose Azevado, Portugal, Once, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
43. Gilberto Simoni, Italy, Lampre, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
44. Oskar Camenzind, Switzerland, Lampre, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
64. Jan Ullrich, Germany, Telekom, 9 seconds behind.  &lt;br&gt;
66. Kevin Livingston, United States, Telekom, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
67. Hernan Buenahora, Colombia, Selle Italia, same time.  &lt;br&gt;
110. Julio Perez Cuapio, Mexico, Ceramiche Panaria, 22 seconds behind.  &lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Final general classification:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

1. Gilberto Simoni, Italy, Lampre, 89 hours, 2 minutes, 58 seconds.  &lt;br&gt;
2. Abraham Olano, Spain, Once, 7 minutes, 31 seconds behind.  &lt;br&gt;
3. Unai Osa Eizaguirre, Spain, Banesto, 8:37.  &lt;br&gt;
4. Sergei Gontchar, Ukraine, Liquigas, 9:25.  &lt;br&gt;
5. Jose Azevedo, Portugal, Once, 9:44.  &lt;br&gt;
6. Andrea Noe, Italy, Mapei, 10:50.  &lt;br&gt;
7. Ivan Gotti, Italy, Alessio, 10:54.  &lt;br&gt;
8. Humberto Carlos Contreras Cano, Colombia, Selle Italia, 11:34.  &lt;br&gt;
9. Pietro Caucchioli, Italy, Alessio, 13:34.  &lt;br&gt;
10. Giuliano Figueras, Italy, Ceramiche Panaria, 14:08.  &lt;br&gt;
11. Marco Velo, Italy, Mercatone Uno, 14:34.  &lt;br&gt;
12. Peter Luttenberger, Austria, Tacconi Sport, 15:36.  &lt;br&gt;
13. Hernan Buenahora, Colombia, Selle Italia, 16:22.  &lt;br&gt;
14. Paolo Savoldelli, Italy, Saeco, 18:42.  &lt;br&gt;
15. Joaquim Romero Castelblanco, Colombia, Selle Italia, 23:02&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Selected riders&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

27. Oskar Camenzind, Switzerland, Lampre, 46.15.  &lt;br&gt;
45. Julio Perez Cuapio, Mexico, Ceramiche Panaria, 1:22:22.  &lt;br&gt;
52. Jan Ullrich, Germany, Telekom, 1:31:22.  &lt;br&gt;
58. Maximilian Sciandri, Britain, Lampre, 1:40:58.  &lt;br&gt;
114. Kevin Livingston, United States, Telekom, 2:30:48.  &lt;br&gt;
124. Guido Trenti, United States, Cantina Tollo, 2:40:18.  &lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="9">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Stage_12__Overall_GC_standings.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Stage_12__Overall_GC_standings.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Stage_12__Overall_GC_standings.htm</UD>
			<T>Stage 12: Overall GC standings</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<S>1. Lance Armstrong (USA/USP)               46 h 47:47.  
&lt;br&gt;2. Joseba Beloki (Spa/ONE)             at       02:28.  
&lt;br&gt;3. Igor Gonzalez Galdeano (Spa/ONE)             03:19.  
&lt;br&gt;4. Raimondas Rumsas (Lit/LAM)                   05:15.  
&lt;br&gt;5. Santiago Botero (Col/KEL)                    05:44.  
&lt;br&gt;6. Marcos Serrano (Spa/ONE)                     07:14.  
&lt;br&gt;7. Roberto Heras (Spa/USP)                      08:01.  
&lt;br&gt;8. Jose Azevedo (Por/ONE)                       08:24.  
&lt;br&gt;9. Oscar Sevilla (Spa/KEL)                      09:05.  
&lt;br&gt;10. Francisco Mancebo (Spa/BAN)                  09:10.  
&lt;br&gt;11. Carlos Sastre (Spa/CST)                      09:32.  
&lt;br&gt;12. Levy Leipheimer (USA/RAB)                    10:41.  
&lt;br&gt;13. David Moncoutie (Fra/COF)                    11:10.  
&lt;br&gt;14. Axel Merckx (Bel/DFF)                        11:26.  
&lt;br&gt;15. Andrei Kivilev (Kaz/COF)                     11:39.  
&lt;br&gt;16. Ivan Basso (Ita/FAS)                         12:29.  
&lt;br&gt;17. Isidro Nozal (Spa/ONE)                       12:39.  
&lt;br&gt;18. Massimiliano Lelli (Ita/COF)                 13:27.  
&lt;br&gt;19. Dario Frigo (Ita/TAC)                        13:34.  
&lt;br&gt;20. Nicolas Vogondy (Fra/FDJ)                    13:36.  
&lt;br&gt;21. Haimar Zubeldia (Spa/EUS)                    13:49.  
&lt;br&gt;22. Tyler Hamilton (USA/CST)                     14:04.  
&lt;br&gt;23. Unai Osa (Spa/BAN)                           14:58.  
&lt;br&gt;24. Stephane Goubert (Fra/DEL)                   14:59.  
&lt;br&gt;25. Richard Virenque (Fra/DFF)                   15:44.  
&lt;br&gt;26. Jose Enrique Gutierrez (Spa/KEL)             16:00.  
&lt;br&gt;27. Jorg Jaksche (Ger/ONE)                       16:19.  
&lt;br&gt;28. Wladimir Belli (Ita/FAS)                     16:44.  
&lt;br&gt;29. Nicki Sorensen (Den/CST)                     17:29.  
&lt;br&gt;30. Laurent Dufaux (Swi/ALS)                     17:33.  
&lt;br&gt;31. Laurent Jalabert (Fra/CST)                   17:43.  
&lt;br&gt;32. Jean-Cyril Robin (Fra/FDJ)                   18:11.  
&lt;br&gt;33. Jose Luis Rubiera (Spa/USP)                  18:19.  
&lt;br&gt;34. Laurent Lefevre (Fra/DEL)                    18:36.  
&lt;br&gt;35. Kevin Livingston (USA/TEL)                   19:28.  
&lt;br&gt;36. Beat Zberg (Swi/RAB)                         19:41.  
&lt;br&gt;37. Piotr Wadecki (Pol/DFF)                      20:03.  
&lt;br&gt;38. Christophe Moreau (Fra/C.A)                  20:12.  
&lt;br&gt;39. Ivan Gotti (Ita/ALS)                         23:01.  
&lt;br&gt;40. Michael Boogerd (Ned/RAB)                    23:08.  
&lt;br&gt;41. Christophe Brandt (Bel/LOT)                  24:20.  
&lt;br&gt;42. Andrea Peron (Ita/CST)                       24:26.  
&lt;br&gt;43. Grischa Niermann (Ger/RAB)                   25:16.  
&lt;br&gt;44. Bobby Julich (USa/TEL)                       25:29.  
&lt;br&gt;45. Dariusz Baranowski (Pol/BAN)                 26:12.  
&lt;br&gt;46. Laurent Brochard (Fra/DEL)                   26:19.  
&lt;br&gt;47. Viatcheslav Ekimov (Rus/USP)                 27:42.  
&lt;br&gt;48. Volodomir Gustov (Ukr/FAS)                   28:16.  
&lt;br&gt;49. Alexandre Botcharov (Rus/A2R)                29:42.  
&lt;br&gt;50. Inigo Chaurreau (Spa/A2R)                    32:08.  
&lt;br&gt;51. Santiago Blanco (Spa/BAN)                    32:27.  
&lt;br&gt;52. Guennadi Mikhailov (Rus/LOT)                 33:33.  
&lt;br&gt;53. Floyd Landis (USA/USP)                       34:19.  
&lt;br&gt;54. Marzio Bruseghin (Ita/BAN)                   36:44.  
&lt;br&gt;55. Inigo Cuesta (Spa/COF)                       37:03.  
&lt;br&gt;56. George Hincapie (USA/USP)                    39:18.  
&lt;br&gt;57. Gerhard Trampusch (Aut/MAP)                  39:32.  
&lt;br&gt;58. Marco Velo (Ita/FAS)                         40:01.  
&lt;br&gt;59. Jerome Pineau (Fra/BJR)                      41:38.  
&lt;br&gt;60. Pavel Padrnos (Cze/USP)                      43:49.  
&lt;br&gt;61. Mario Aerts (Bel/LOT)                        45:01.  
&lt;br&gt;62. Erik Zabel (Ger/TEL)                         45:21.  
&lt;br&gt;63. Sylvain Chavanel (Fra/BJR)                   46:00.  
&lt;br&gt;64. Gianluca Bortolami (Ita/TAC)                 46:25.  
&lt;br&gt;65. Franck Renier (Fra/BJR)                      46:26.  
&lt;br&gt;66. Serhiy Honchar (Ukr/FAS)                     46:27.  
&lt;br&gt;67. Dave Bruylandts (Bel/DFF)                    47:04.  
&lt;br&gt;68. Rolf Aldag (Ger/TEL)                         47:43.  
&lt;br&gt;69. Abraham Olano (Spa/ONE)                      47:48.  
&lt;br&gt;70. Bingen Fernandez (Spa/COF)                   48:39.  
&lt;br&gt;71. Roberto Laiseka (Spa/EUS)                    49:16.  
&lt;br&gt;72. Miguel Martinez (Fra/MAP)                    49:35.  
&lt;br&gt;73. Stuart O'Grady (Aus/C.A)                     50:01.  
&lt;br&gt;74. David Millar (Gbr/COF)                       50:20.  
&lt;br&gt;75. Victor Hugo Pena (Col/USP)                   50:46.  
&lt;br&gt;76. Tomas Konecny (Cze/DFF)                      50:51.  
&lt;br&gt;77. Serguei Ivanov (Rus/FAS)                     52:34.  
&lt;br&gt;78. Marc Wauters (Bel/RAB)                       52:35.  
&lt;br&gt;79. Denis Menchov (Rus/BAN)                      52:46.  
&lt;br&gt;80. David Latasa (Spa/BAN)                       53:00.  
&lt;br&gt;81. Benoit Joachim (Lux/USP)                     53:07.  
&lt;br&gt;82. Giuseppe Guerini (Ita/TEL)                   53:52.  
&lt;br&gt;83. Cristian Moreni (Ita/ALS)                    54:36.  
&lt;br&gt;84. Javier Pascual Rodriguez (Spa/BAN)           54:44.  
&lt;br&gt;85. Danilo Hondo (Ger/TEL)                       54:49.  
&lt;br&gt;86. David Etxebarria (Spa/EUS)                   54:57.  
&lt;br&gt;87. Laszlo Bodrogi (Hun/MAP)                     55:16.  
&lt;br&gt;88. Jerome Bernard (Fra/DEL)                     55:37.  
&lt;br&gt;89. Udo Bolts (Ger/TEL)                          56:01.  
&lt;br&gt;90. Steffen Wesemann (Ger/TEL)                   56:03.  
&lt;br&gt;91. Daniel Atienza (Spa/COF)                     56:07.  
&lt;br&gt;92. Bradley McGee (Aus/FDJ)                      56:14.  
&lt;br&gt;93. Patrice Halgand (Fra/DEL)                    58:40.  
&lt;br&gt;94. Anthony Morin (Fra/C.A)                      58:57.  
&lt;br&gt;95. Ludovic Turpin (Fra/A2R)                     59:02.  
&lt;br&gt;96. Robert Hunter (Rsa/MAP)                      59:21.  
&lt;br&gt;97. Frederic Bessy (Fra/C.A)                   1h00:41.  
&lt;br&gt;98. Walter Beneteau (Fra/BJR)                  1h02:45.  
&lt;br&gt;99. Marco Serpellini (Ita/LAM)                 1h03:00.  
&lt;br&gt;100. Jens Voigt (Ger/C.A)                       1h04:40.  
&lt;br&gt;101. Christophe Mengin (Fra/FDJ)                1h07:03.  
&lt;br&gt;102. Sandy Casar (Fra/FDJ)                      1h07:57.  
&lt;br&gt;103. Francisco Cabello (Spa/KEL)                1h08:09.  
&lt;br&gt;104. Jose Javier Gomez (Spa/KEL)                1h08:11.  
&lt;br&gt;105. Mikel Pradera (Spa/ONE)                    1h08:44.  
&lt;br&gt;106. Andy Flickinger (Fra/A2R)                  1h08:56.  
&lt;br&gt;107. Cedric Vasseur (Fra/COF)                   1h10:08.  
&lt;br&gt;108. Serge Baguet (Bel/LOT)                     1h10:27.  
&lt;br&gt;109. Ludo Dierckxsens (Bel/LAM)                 1h10:50.  
&lt;br&gt;110. Pedro Horillo (Spa/MAP)                    1h10:50.  
&lt;br&gt;111. Franck Bouyer (Fra/BJR)                    1h10:54.  
&lt;br&gt;112. Christophe Edaleine (Fra/DEL)              1h10:54.  
&lt;br&gt;113. Gian Matteo Fagnini (Ita/TEL)              1h11:12.  
&lt;br&gt;114. Eddy Mazzoleni (Ita/TAC)                   1h11:23.  
&lt;br&gt;115. Frederic Guesdon (Fra/FDJ)                 1h11:37.  
&lt;br&gt;116. Iban Mayo (Spa/EUS)                        1h11:52.  
&lt;br&gt;117. Constantino Zaballa (Spa/KEL)              1h12:09.  
&lt;br&gt;118. Raivis Belohvosciks (Lat/LAM)              1h12:52.  
&lt;br&gt;119. Nico Mattan (Bel/COF)                      1h13:03.  
&lt;br&gt;120. Paul Van Hyfte (Bel/CST)                   1h13:18.  
&lt;br&gt;121. Addy Engels (Ned/RAB)                      1h13:44.  
&lt;br&gt;122. Enrico Cassani (Ita/DFF)                   1h13:58.  
&lt;br&gt;123. Andrea Brognara (Ita/ALS)                  1h15:14.  
&lt;br&gt;124. Baden Cooke (Aus/FDJ)                      1h16:49.  
&lt;br&gt;125. Emmanuel Magnien (Fra/BJR)                 1h17:25.  
&lt;br&gt;126. Robbie McEwen (Aus/LOT)                    1h17:48.  
&lt;br&gt;127. Peter Luttenberger (Aut/TAC)               1h18:12.  
&lt;br&gt;128. Andrea Tafi (Ita/MAP)                      1h20:19.  
&lt;br&gt;129. Jan Svorada (Cze/LAM)                      1h20:28.  
&lt;br&gt;130. Rubens Bertogliati (Swi/LAM)               1h20:29.  
&lt;br&gt;131. Fred Rodriguez (USA/DFF)                   1h21:01.  
&lt;br&gt;132. Thierry Loder (Fra/A2R)                    1h21:22.  
&lt;br&gt;133. Massimo Donati (Ita/TAC)                   1h21:36.  
&lt;br&gt;134. Jakob Piil (Den/CST)                       1h21:52.  
&lt;br&gt;135. Vicente Garcia-Acosta (Spa/BAN)            1h22:20.  
&lt;br&gt;136. Nicola Loda (Ita/FAS)                      1h22:25.  
&lt;br&gt;137. Cyril Dessel (Fra/DEL)                     1h23:54.  
&lt;br&gt;138. Karsten Kroon (Ned/RAB)                    1h24:13.  
&lt;br&gt;139. Christophe Oriol (Fra/A2R)                 1h25:31.  
&lt;br&gt;140. Mauro Radaelli (Ita/TAC)                   1h26:07.  
&lt;br&gt;141. Massimo Apollonio (Ita/TAC)                1h26:59.  
&lt;br&gt;142. Stephane Auge (Fra/DEL)                    1h27:17.  
&lt;br&gt;143. Jose Angel Vidal (Spa/KEL)                 1h27:23.  
&lt;br&gt;144. Davide Casarotto (Ita/ALS)                 1h27:25.  
&lt;br&gt;145. Hans De Clercq (Bel/LOT)                   1h27:26.  
&lt;br&gt;146. Alessandro Cortinovis (Ita/LAM)            1h27:55.  
&lt;br&gt;147. Gorka Arrizabalaga (Spa/EUS)               1h27:58.  
&lt;br&gt;148. Servais Knaven (Ned/DFF)                   1h28:59.  
&lt;br&gt;149. Unai Etxebarria (Ven/EUS)                  1h29:20.  
&lt;br&gt;150. Fabio Baldato (Ita/FAS)                    1h29:42.  
&lt;br&gt;151. Leon Van Bon (Ned/DFF)                     1h30:38.  
&lt;br&gt;152. Jacky Durand (Fra/FDJ)                     1h30:41.  
&lt;br&gt;153. Eddy Seigneur (Fra/DEL)                    1h31:08.  
&lt;br&gt;154. Bram De Groot (Ned/RAB)                    1h31:10.  
&lt;br&gt;155. Sebastien Hinault (Fra/C.A)                1h31:11.  
&lt;br&gt;156. Martin Hvastija (Slo/ALS)                  1h33:17.  
&lt;br&gt;157. Jimmy Casper (Fra/FDJ)                     1h33:24.  
&lt;br&gt;158. Thierry Marichal (Bel/LOT)                 1h34:13.  
&lt;br&gt;159. Christophe Agnolutto (Fra/A2R)             1h34:53.  
&lt;br&gt;160. Paolo Bossoni (Ita/TAC)                    1h35:25.  
&lt;br&gt;161. Anthony Langella (Fra/C.A)                 1h37:18.  
&lt;br&gt;162. Erik Dekker (Ned/RAB)                      1h39:02.  
&lt;br&gt;163. Igor Flores (Spa/EUS)                      1h41:59.  
&lt;br&gt;164. Damien Nazon (Fra/BJR)                     1h43:20.  
&lt;br&gt;165. Arvis Piziks (Lat/CST)                     1h43:45.  
&lt;br&gt;166. Thor Hushovd (Nor/C.A)                     1h45:54.  
&lt;br&gt;167. Stephane Berges (Fra/A2R)                  1h57:15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="10">
			<U>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/ENDURANCE_4-FLASK_BELT_FROM_FUELBELT_br__em_No_bounce__no_play__em_.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/ENDURANCE_4-FLASK_BELT_FROM_FUELBELT_br__em_No_bounce__no_play__em_.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/gear/Articles/ENDURANCE_4-FLASK_BELT_FROM_FUELBELT_br__em_No_bounce__no_play__em_.htm</UD>
			<T>ENDURANCE 4-FLASK BELT FROM FUELBELT&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;No bounce, no play&lt;/em&gt;</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The Endurance 4-Flask Belt from FuelBelt has a lot of the unique qualities that I look for in a hydration belt. After running with it for over 300 miles of training and racing, it's earned a spot in my gear collection."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Gear"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=40332"/>
			<S>Over the past couple of years I've managed to collect an assortment of running gear that has even begun to boggle &lt;em&gt;my&lt;/em&gt; mind. The overflow of shoes alone, in varying states of decay, leaves my family and friends bewildered. Bottles, belts, apparel, nutrition products, you name it. It's all here. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow I can't bring myself to toss this stuff out to make room for the new, because each item, at one point, possessed a unique quality that I thought was handy, comfortable or just plain cool.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;Well, I have a new piece of equipment that has managed to capture a lot of the unique qualities that I look for in a hydration belt, and after running with the Endurance 4-Flask Belt from FuelBelt for over 300 miles of training and racing on all kinds of terrain, it has earned a special place in my closet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="subhead"&gt;Overall construction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 4-Flask Belt has four, seven-oz. flasks dispersed evenly, with two on the back and two on the front. The belt itself is a rugged two-inch band of elastic material that is secured by over three inches of Velcro that meets in the front of the waist. Each flask holder on the belt securely holds the flasks in place, and allows you to stretch a nylon cord over the tip of the flask if needed.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;!--insertad--&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For training runs of 2 to 2.5 hours, I typically will carry a water bottle in my hand(s), and just hold energy gels wherever I can find space.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By wearing a Fuel Belt, that's 28 oz. of liquids that I don't have to carry in standard 20-oz. bottles in my hands, and the generous rear pocket that sits in the center of the back frees up my hands by holding my gels, salt and keys. Here are the specifics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No bounce! Really!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Even with 28 oz. of liquids hooked into the belt, I experienced no bounce or play in the belt when I began my runs. Let me assure you that I didn't just run around the block to find this out ... I ran pavement, fire roads, single track, over rocks and fallen trees, up, down and all around. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially I was worried that the belt would ride up off of my hips when my body was contorted to accommodate the terrain, but this didn't happen. When ascending a very steep grade, the two front flasks did push slightly into my midsection and onto the top of my quadriceps, but this wasn't enough to move things around.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wow, I'm thirsty, where's my flask?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This belt model has the flasks positioned so that there's no chance of smacking your sweaty hands on them if your arms drift low to your sides. This is particularly helpful when ascending as your legs bend and your center of mass shifts slightly lower to the ground. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found the holding cords for the flasks a neat feature, but not really necessary -- even if I was jumping off of a three-foot tree stump. The flask-holders on the belt itself do a great job of keeping things in place, so I just left them unhooked for easier access with one hand.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tough as nails&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This belt took some serious abuse. I made a point to "aggressively" jam the flasks into their holders, and there's no sign of fatigue in the stitching or degradation in the strength of the hold. The belt itself is no worse for the wear, and mysteriously does not stink like some other equipment I have that's been sweated into. Hmm, maybe I just can't tell anymore?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I &lt;em&gt;thought&lt;/em&gt; I brought something to eat!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The rear pocket seems to be just the right size for a 2- to 2.5-hour run. I was able to comfortably fit an energy bar, a coin pouch to hold salt tablets and my keys. At one point I jammed two energy bars, one gel, salt and keys -- which caused my gel to burst! (Very messy. My keys will never be the same.) The pouch is made of neoprene with two sections separated by Velcro, so even if you only put your keys inside, you won't be jingling your way down the trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I'll report back after the next 300 miles ...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
Whether you are the casual athlete or a serious competitor, you have every right to be picky, and demand ideal performance from your running gear. Of course there will always be tradeoffs in the details you like, but the Endurance 4-Flask Belt will not disappoint you for that two-hour trail run in the boonies. It has a snug fit, ample liquid storage, stable weight distribution, and trusty pocket for your Gameboy (well, maybe not).&lt;/p&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="11">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Use_a_heart_rate_monitor_wisely_to_avoid_over-_or_under-training.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Use_a_heart_rate_monitor_wisely_to_avoid_over-_or_under-training.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/Use_a_heart_rate_monitor_wisely_to_avoid_over-_or_under-training.htm</UD>
			<T>Use a heart rate monitor wisely to avoid over- or under-training</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="&quot;The more I work with cyclists who use heart-rate monitors,&quot; says cycling doc Ed Burke, &quot;the more I realize that many cyclists train too hard or too easily because they do not realize the many factors that can affect heart rate.&quot;"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=39417"/>
			<S>The more I work with cyclists who use heart-rate monitors, the more I realize that many cyclists train too hard or too easily because they do not realize the many factors that can affect heart rate.&lt;p&gt;

Let's look at five ways to use your heart-rate monitor effectively to improve your cycling performance.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;1. Measure your heart rate during easy rides to safeguard against overtraining.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

The purpose of your easy ride is to recover from the stress of hard training and racing. If you do these rides too hard (as many cyclists do), you will become overtrained, with staleness eventually setting in. You can avoid this problem by tracking your heart rate on your easy days. Let's say you typically ride 20 miles in 60 minutes at a heart rate of 155 beats per minute (bpm). One day, however, you find your heart rate is 165 bpm during your regular one-hour ride. That is most likely a sign that you should back off for a couple of days before doing your next hard workout or race. You may be overtrained or fighting a bug.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;2. Don't use a formula to determine your maximal heart rate.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

You need to know your maximal heart rate (MHR) to set correct training levels. Several formulas exist to predict MHR; all have flaws. The formulas were developed using regression equations, which means that if 100 cyclists estimate their MHR using a formula, the average will be just about right; the MHR for an individual, however, could be off by up to 20 bpm.&lt;p&gt;

Recently, a 30-year-old cyclist came to me for a training program. His estimated MHR, based on the 220-minus-age formula, was 190 bpm. But when he rode twice for four minutes hard uphill, his heart rate went up to 197 bpm  7 bpm higher than the formula predicted. Formulas also can overestimate MHR, as in the case of a 20-year-old cyclist who could only get his heart rate up to 191 bpm.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;3. Don't select your heart rate for racing based on measurements taken during training.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

Two studies from an international conference on the use of heart-rate monitors, published in the &lt;i&gt;Journal of Sports Sciences&lt;/i&gt;, reported that heart rate during racing is substantially higher than during training at the same pace. One study, from the Sports Science Institute of South Africa, found heart rates measured during a 10K running race to be 20 bpm higher than while training at the same speed; during a marathon the rates were 19 bpm higher than when training at marathon race pace.&lt;p&gt;

The researchers write, "The heart rate difference could not be explained by differences in terrain or added psychological stress."&lt;p&gt;

Several researchers speculate that increased psychological arousal in the races can account for the difference. This suggests that the excitement of racing accounts, at least in part, for the higher heart rates.&lt;p&gt;

The upshot is that using training heart rates to select race paces will lead to slower-than-anticipated race times. As a result, you could end up racing several miles per hour slower than your pace at the same heart rate during training  and that could turn into a much slower pace, let's say in a time trial! This phenomenon in reverse can work against you too. For example, if you base your heart rate for tempo rides on your heart rate during a 10-mile race, you may end up doing your tempo rides too fast.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;4. Remember that your heart rate increases as you become dehydrated.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

This phenomenon, called cardiac drift, occurs because dehydration causes a drop in blood volume, which means less blood is pumped with each heartbeat. A study published in the &lt;i&gt;Journal of Applied Physiology&lt;/i&gt; found that heart rate increases seven beats per minute for each 1 percent loss in body weight due to dehydration.&lt;p&gt;

Cycling for one hour in 70-degree heat can result in a loss of 1.5 to 3 pounds. That's a 1 percent to 2 percent weight loss for a 150-pound cyclist, which would increase heart rate by seven to 14 bpm.&lt;p&gt;

If this cyclist is planning a tempo ride at a heart rate of 150 to 155 bpm, she should account for the fact that her pace will slow during the ride, and allow her heart rate to increase to about 160 to 175 bpm by the end.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Want to ride 100 miles? Check out our &lt;a href="http://www.active.com/century_challenge/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Century Challenge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Online training diary. Use our&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.active.com/activetrainer/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Active trainer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;b&gt;to record your mileage and vital stats.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;p&gt; 

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;b&gt;Shop for cycling gear and much more at the&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.activesportsmecca.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Active Sports Mecca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;img src="/images/global/bugs/arrow_gold.gif" align=center&gt; &lt;a href="/advanced_search.cfm" align=center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Find and register for a bike tour or race in your area!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="12">
			<U>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/_Windless__eyewear___The_next_innovation_in_cycling_sunglasses.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/_Windless__eyewear___The_next_innovation_in_cycling_sunglasses.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/cycling/Articles/_Windless__eyewear___The_next_innovation_in_cycling_sunglasses.htm</UD>
			<T>'Windless' eyewear:  The next innovation in cycling sunglasses</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="UV rays aren't the only danger to cyclists' eyes. Wind and wind-borne stuff can cause damage as well. Here's a look at the possible risks, and what some sunglass companies are doing about it."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/AssetFactory.aspx?did=39072"/>
			<S>For several years now, the sunglass industry has responded to the needs of cycling enthusiasts by offering lenses with 99 to 100 percent UV blockage and shield or wraparound designs to block most of the UV waves.&lt;/p&gt;
 
&lt;p&gt;However, several companies are taking eye protection even further by 
developing a sunglass that fully protects the eyes with orbital foam seals, 
completely preventing UV from reaching the eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There may be several other benefits to such an approach, as it also provides protection against another environmental factor: wind! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cycling downhill or into headwinds at high speeds can provide near 
hurricane-force wind in the face. In addition to dangers of sunlight and UV, 
there is evidence that the long-term effects of wind exposure can be 
damaging to both skin and the eye. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The phenomenon of "windburn"  getting more sunburn on a windy day  is a common experience and has serious consequences for your eyesight. There is evidence that wind and heat can accelerate the carcinogenic (cancer-causing) effect of UV radiation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, protecting the skin around the eyes from both sun and wind can further minimize damage and aging effects from UV exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the American Academy of Ophthalmology, pterygia and  pingueculae (abnormal growths on the outside surface of the eye that can impair vision) are more common in people exposed to wind and bright sun. Pterygia, sometimes referred to as "triangles" due to their shape, and pingueculae, often a precursor of pterygia, are believed to be associated with microtrauma to the outer surface of the eye from exposure to sunlight and/or dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Factors that can contribute to the condition include sunny, sandy, windblown or dusty locations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Blink rate&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Wind also causes us to tear and increase our rate of blinking, in an effort to compensate for the drying effects of continuous wind exposure. While these responses may help to temporarily reduce discomfort, they can reduce our ability to see clearly, compromising peak visual performance. Tearing distorts images by producing numerous optical aberrations. Increased blinking significantly reduces the overall amount of image information, as every blink is in effect a brief visual blackout! Normal blink rates accelerate when wind increases, cutting visual acuity and lowering color perception. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Contact lenses &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Another effect of wind can be to dry out and/or displace contact lenses, making clear vision impossible. Even after the wind diminishes, the lens often will not return to its proper position without assistance. The drying effect alone can be extremely discomforting to contact lens wearers, to the point where blinking can start to become painful. Dust and pollen can further degrade the comfort of the contact lenses.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Allergies&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
According to the American Academy of Ophthalmology, Seasonal Allergic  Conjunctivitis, or allergy eyes, is a medical condition in which the eyes respond to allergens (pollen), causing any or all of the following symptoms: swelling, redness, burning and the sensation that something is in the eye. Cycling exposes the eye to a barrage of dust, pollen and exhaust fumes. These elements can be especially discomforting with contact lens wearers, allergy sufferers and people with dry eye syndrome. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dry eye&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; 
It is estimated that 10 million Americans suffer from dry eye syndrome, with allergy sufferers and contact lens wearers at higher risk. Dry eye syndrome is a decline of the quality or quantity of tears bathing the eye. This condition can lead to constant pain from eye irritation and a sandy or gritty sensation. Untreated dry eye can lead to scarring or ulceration of the cornea and thus loss of vision. Sunglasses with foam seals are designed to protect the eyes from wind-borne dust and pollen and can mitigate these conditions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Windless is better &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several major brands of sunglass companies are engineering glasses that comfortably seals the eye, enhancing visual acuity and protection for individuals in high speed and motion activities  sheltering the eyes from wind, dust, snow, pollen and road debris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have tested several of these and find them quite comfortable for cycling.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Panoptx Venturi&lt;/b&gt;: This sunglass offers the most wind protection with medical grade foam that completely encloses and protects the eye. It has a patented adjustable venting system that controls the amount of wind that reaches the eyes. &lt;I&gt;www.panoptx.com&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rudy Project Ekynox&lt;/b&gt;: This well-known brand in the cycling community offers a foam insert that surrounds the lenses' frame area and comes with removable and interchangeable lenses for cycling in various light conditions.  Additional lenses must be purchased separately. &lt;i&gt;www.rudyprojectusa.com&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zeal Lazor&lt;/b&gt;: This performance sunglass comes with a top sweat guard that can serve as a partial wind block. Comes with three interchangeable lenses for varying light conditions and travel case. &lt;i&gt;www.zealoptics.com&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="13">
			<U>http://www.active.com/outdoors/Articles/Your_favorite_outdoor_playground_can_be_a_classroom__too.htm</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/outdoors/Articles/Your_favorite_outdoor_playground_can_be_a_classroom__too.htm</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/outdoors/Articles/Your_favorite_outdoor_playground_can_be_a_classroom__too.htm</UD>
			<T>Your favorite outdoor playground can be a classroom, too</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Like most outdoor enthusiasts, you probably care deeply about the natural world. The next time you visit your favorite outdoor playground, try refocusing your nature microscope with a sport I call &lt;i&gt;ecostudy&lt;/i&gt;."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Articles"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Outdoors"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Article"/>
			<S>Like most outdoor enthusiasts, you probably care deeply about the natural world. After all, no one wants to canoe in a stream that reeks of industrial pollutants or backpack through a parking lot.&lt;p&gt;

But how often do you really observe what's beyond the scenic landscape? The next time you visit your favorite outdoor playground, try refocusing your nature microscope with a sport I call &lt;i&gt;ecostudy&lt;/i&gt;. It used to be known as nature study, and was considered the domain of nerds wearing pith helmets and carrying butterfly nets. But observing and understanding more about the natural world will enrich any outdoor activity and may provide crucial information to help us better protect and manage our environment.&lt;p&gt;

Ecostudy, by any name, has a long and noble history. Charles Darwin made some of his most important observations and discoveries long after the legendary voyage of the HMS Beagle. Darwin's garden, in Kent, England, was one of his most cherished places, and he studied it as much for science as for pleasure.&lt;p&gt;

Even latter-day conservationists such as Aldo Leopold have suggested incorporating the study of the natural world into recreational activities. In his book, &lt;i&gt;A Sand County Almanac&lt;/i&gt;, Leopold proposed wildlife research as a new form of outdoor sport: "In the biological field the sport-value of amateur research is just beginning to be realized."&lt;p&gt;

He cited the accomplishments of a banker who banded bald eagles and a cattle rancher who wrote one of the first authoritative books on mountain lions. Leopold himself participated in recreational wildlife research, banding birds, and reintroducing native plants to his beloved farm. He even turned the act of cutting an oak tree for firewood into an ecological history lesson.&lt;p&gt;

Likewise, forester and conservationist Bob Marshall, one of the founders of the Wilderness Society, spent much of his life studying the wilderness areas of the West and of Alaska. He combined his professional activities with his passion for hiking, often covering 35 or 40 miles in a single day.&lt;p&gt;

Of course, you don't need to be a professional scientist to participate in an ecostudy project. Many state environmental and wildlife agencies can provide information and sometimes even equipment to help you get started on projects such as collecting water-quality data or looking for signs of rare or recently reintroduced species in parks and forests.&lt;p&gt;

Perhaps the first and best-known program is the National Audubon Society's Christmas Bird Count, which has provided long-term annual data on numerous bird species. Similarly, the precipitous decline of amphibians in many parts of the United States and around the world has prompted the establishment of monitoring networks in virtually every state.&lt;p&gt;

Most of these depend on volunteers to conduct call counts for frogs and toads or check artificial cover stations (usually boards laid in the woods) for amphibians. The beauty of ecostudy projects like these is that you can easily work them into other outdoor activities, such as fishing, hiking, or canoeing.&lt;p&gt;

 I've been participating in my own ecostudy projects for years. I've done them while camping in the Ozarks, hiking in the Bighorns, and fishing in the Gulf of Mexico. My favorite place by far for ecostudy is the little-known Weeks Bay National Estuarine Research Reserve near Fairhope, Ala. Nestled serenely off the southeastern corner of Mobile Bay, it remains one of the Gulf Coast's best-kept natural secrets.&lt;p&gt;

The reserve was established in 1986 through a cooperative effort between the state of Alabama, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Association, and dedicated local conservationists. As its name implies, the function of the reserve is to protect the Weeks Bay estuary, while also providing an outdoor laboratory for teaching and research. These joint missions of protection and education make this an ideal site for ecostudy activities.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Next: Outdoor study at Weeks Bay research reserve&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="14">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/wmrebelfootball</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/wmrebelfootball</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/wmrebelfootball</UD>
			<T>West Monroe Rebels</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="West Monroe High School Sports Site."/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Baseball"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Varsity"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="High School\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="West  Monroe"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Louisiana"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="15">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/RockyRiverGators</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/RockyRiverGators</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/RockyRiverGators</UD>
			<T>RockyRiverGators</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Baseball"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Youth 11u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Tournament\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Concord"/>
			<MT N="state" V="North Carolina"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="16">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/ROWolverines</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/ROWolverines</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/ROWolverines</UD>
			<T>Royal Oak Wolverines Team 63</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Ice Hockey"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Youth 12u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Recreational\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Royal Oak"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Michigan"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="17">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/12U_bedford_hornets</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/12U_bedford_hornets</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/12U_bedford_hornets</UD>
			<T>12U Bedford Hornets</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="This site is designed for the 20062007 12U Bedford Hornets."/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Softball\Fast Pitch"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="female,Youth 12u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Competitive\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Bedford"/>
			<MT N="state" V="New Hampshire"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="18">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/nkscexplosion96</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/nkscexplosion96</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/nkscexplosion96</UD>
			<T>Explosion 96</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Elementary youth soccer team led by Don Sweeney."/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Soccer"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Youth 11u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Elementary\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Kingston"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Washington"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="19">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/tcsbaseball</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/tcsbaseball</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/tcsbaseball</UD>
			<T>TCS EAGLES</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Varsity Baseball"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Baseball"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Varsity"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="High School\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Holland"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Ohio"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="20">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/dteamsoftball</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/dteamsoftball</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/dteamsoftball</UD>
			<T>Columbus Fire D</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Softball\Slow Pitch"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Adult"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Competitive\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Grove City"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Ohio"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="21">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/bsaCosmosU15girls</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/bsaCosmosU15girls</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/bsaCosmosU15girls</UD>
			<T>Cosmos</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Soccer"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="female,Youth 15u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Competitive\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Waukesha"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Wisconsin"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="22">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/nheastsquirt2</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/nheastsquirt2</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/nheastsquirt2</UD>
			<T>NHE Squirt 2</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Ice Hockey"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="coed,Youth 10u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Elementary\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Kingston"/>
			<MT N="state" V="New Hampshire"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="23">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/westfieldU15</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/westfieldU15</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/westfieldU15</UD>
			<T>Westfield Youth FC</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Football site for Westfield Youth FC members of the West Surrey Boys League  Surrey County FA ENGLAND"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Soccer"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Youth 16u"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Competitive\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Woking"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Surrey"/>
			<MT N="country" V="England"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="24">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/VisionEliteTC</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/VisionEliteTC</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/VisionEliteTC</UD>
			<T>Vision Elite Track Club</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="coed,All Ages"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Upper Marlboro"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Maryland"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="25">
			<U>http://eteamz.active.com/sheehan-titans</U>
			<UE>http://eteamz.active.com/sheehan-titans</UE>
			<UD>http://eteamz.active.com/sheehan-titans</UD>
			<T>SheehanTitans</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Sponsored by the Dugout Club This site is dedicated to the Mark T. Sheehan High School Baseball program its players, coaches and supporters"/>
			<MT N="category" V="eteamz Sites"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Baseball"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="male,Varsity"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="High School\Team"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Yalesville"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Connecticut"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://eteamz.active.com/p.gif"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="26">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F5E2825F-884C-426A-AF09-80CA306EE1A6</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F5E2825F-884C-426A-AF09-80CA306EE1A6</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F5E2825F-884C-426A-AF09-80CA306EE1A6</UD>
			<T>Fremont Pool</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Swimming Pools - Indoor"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Athletic\Pool"/>
			<MT N="address" V="7630 Towne Avenue"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90003"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="Fremont.Pool@lacity.org"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 847-3401"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="27">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9660C0C0-99B3-4A9E-8011-B3B6F433CC69</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9660C0C0-99B3-4A9E-8011-B3B6F433CC69</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9660C0C0-99B3-4A9E-8011-B3B6F433CC69</UD>
			<T>Green Meadows Pool</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Swimming Pools - Outdoor"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Athletic\Pool"/>
			<MT N="address" V="431 E. 89th Street"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90003"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(323) 789-2726"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="28">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=74A5788D-E6BF-421D-BA95-BE03FD043F43</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=74A5788D-E6BF-421D-BA95-BE03FD043F43</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=74A5788D-E6BF-421D-BA95-BE03FD043F43</UD>
			<T>Green Meadows Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Football Fields Soccer Fields Basketball Courts Tennis Courts - Outdoor Baseball Field Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground Lit at Night"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Community\Park &amp; Rec Facilities"/>
			<MT N="address" V="431 East 89th St."/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90003"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="GreenMeadows.RecreationCenter@lacity.org"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(323) 750-4820"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="29">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=2A07C951-93E8-43AC-8B35-364ED097D92C</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=2A07C951-93E8-43AC-8B35-364ED097D92C</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=2A07C951-93E8-43AC-8B35-364ED097D92C</UD>
			<T>Robert L. Burns Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="4900 Beverly Blvd"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90004"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 847-3599"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="30">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4B6193D8-596E-4C49-8059-52C6B457673A</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4B6193D8-596E-4C49-8059-52C6B457673A</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4B6193D8-596E-4C49-8059-52C6B457673A</UD>
			<T>Harold A. Henry Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="890 South Lucerne Blvd"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90005"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 485-5054"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="31">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=6CF80439-4707-4129-AE99-01481B5512A8</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=6CF80439-4707-4129-AE99-01481B5512A8</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=6CF80439-4707-4129-AE99-01481B5512A8</UD>
			<T>Ardmore Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Basketball Courts Running Track - Outdoor Baseball Field Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground Lit at Night"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Community\Park &amp; Rec Facilities"/>
			<MT N="address" V="3250 San Marino Street"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90006"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="Ardmore.RecreationCenter@lacity.org"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 383-7549"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="32">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A2207DE9-A0E3-415A-BEA7-80F524C39400</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A2207DE9-A0E3-415A-BEA7-80F524C39400</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A2207DE9-A0E3-415A-BEA7-80F524C39400</UD>
			<T>Pico Union Vest Pocket</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="1827 South Hoover Street"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90006"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 485-5054"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="33">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A4064783-67FE-4E6B-9B28-B4C14F67F456</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A4064783-67FE-4E6B-9B28-B4C14F67F456</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A4064783-67FE-4E6B-9B28-B4C14F67F456</UD>
			<T>Terrace Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="Malvern Ave &amp; Alvarado Terrace"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90006"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="34">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=45B80560-DD78-4C03-B32D-01BC448D5584</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=45B80560-DD78-4C03-B32D-01BC448D5584</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=45B80560-DD78-4C03-B32D-01BC448D5584</UD>
			<T>Richardson Family Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Basketball Courts Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="2700 Budlong Avenue"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90007"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 485-5054"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="35">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=0FD18DAB-FD6A-40D7-A39D-2B36EDAACBAE</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=0FD18DAB-FD6A-40D7-A39D-2B36EDAACBAE</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=0FD18DAB-FD6A-40D7-A39D-2B36EDAACBAE</UD>
			<T>Hoover Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Basketball Courts Picnic Area - Uncovered Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Community\Park &amp; Rec Facilities"/>
			<MT N="address" V="1010 West 25th St."/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90007"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="Hoover.RecreationCenter@lacity.org"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 749-8896"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="36">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9C68BDD6-F52D-4EEB-A03D-811D6EB72566</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9C68BDD6-F52D-4EEB-A03D-811D6EB72566</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9C68BDD6-F52D-4EEB-A03D-811D6EB72566</UD>
			<T>Saint James Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Playground"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="Adams Blvd"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90007"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(213) 485-5054"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="37">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=71E95030-79FE-4677-8141-066B6DEAC742</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=71E95030-79FE-4677-8141-066B6DEAC742</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=71E95030-79FE-4677-8141-066B6DEAC742</UD>
			<T>Leimert Plaza Park</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Facilities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services\Parks &amp; Recs"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Picnic Area - Uncovered"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Outdoors\Park"/>
			<MT N="address" V="4395 Leimert Blvd"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90008"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(323) 292-6622"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
		<R N="38">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=7</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=7</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=7</UD>
			<T>Intermediate Olympic Distance Tri Program: 4.75 to 7 hrs/wk - Crash Plan - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="There is an Olympic distance triathlon (swim 1500 meters, bike 24.8 miles, run 6.2 miles) in a nearby city. The event is only six weeks away. Is there enough time to make your triathlon debut? While I usually encourage first-timers to try a sprint distance event before moving to Olympic status, a reasonably fit person can be ready to race in five to six weeks. Want to tri? This six-week crash training plan is designed for a person who maintains their health and remains fit throughout the year. Your fitness might include some combination of running, spin classes or outdoor biking. You may currently swim a few laps or have swimming experience from past years. You may also be involved in other sports. Your current regimen gives you the capability to run for about 30 minutes, twice per week. Your can bike comfortably for about an hour. If your race is held in open water, you must be comfortable swimming in an open water situation. Given the assumptions in the last paragraph, the goal is to complete an Olympic distance triathlon in about six weeks, with a race finish time between three and four hours. The estimated finish time comes from assuming a two to three minute pace per 100 meters for the 1500-meter swim. This puts total swim time between 30 and 45 minutes. If you are capable of riding a bike for about 25 miles, averaging 15 to 18 miles per hour, the bike leg of the race will take around 1:22 to 1:40. Finally the run, averaging 10 to 12 minute miles, will take 1:02 to 1:15. Throw in a few minutes for transition time and the event will total some three to four hours. Originally appeared in the May 2000 issues of 'Triathlete' magazine. Plan is available in the book 'Training Plans for Multisport Athletes'.--------------------Training volume:"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Olympic Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/GaleBernhardt.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$34.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Intermediate"/>
			<S>There is an Olympic distance triathlon (swim 1500 meters, bike 24.8 miles, run 6.2 miles) in a nearby city. The event is only six weeks away. Is there enough time to make your triathlon debut? While I usually encourage first-timers to try a sprint distance event before moving to Olympic status, a reasonably fit person can be ready to race in five to six weeks. Want to tri? This six-week crash training plan is designed for a person who maintains their health and remains fit throughout the year. Your fitness might include some combination of running, spin classes or outdoor biking. You may currently swim a few laps or have swimming experience from past years. You may also be involved in other sports. Your current regimen gives you the capability to run for about 30 minutes, twice per week. Your can bike comfortably for about an hour. If your race is held in open water, you must be comfortable swimming in an open water situation. Given the assumptions in the last paragraph, the goal is to complete an Olympic distance triathlon in about six weeks, with a race finish time between three and four hours. The estimated finish time comes from assuming a two to three minute pace per 100 meters for the 1500-meter swim. This puts total swim time between 30 and 45 minutes. If you are capable of riding a bike for about 25 miles, averaging 15 to 18 miles per hour, the bike leg of the race will take around 1:22 to 1:40. Finally the run, averaging 10 to 12 minute miles, will take 1:02 to 1:15. Throw in a few minutes for transition time and the event will total some three to four hours. Originally appeared in the May 2000 issues of 'Triathlete' magazine. Plan is available in the book 'Training Plans for Multisport Athletes'.--------------------Training volume:</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="39">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=37</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=37</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=37</UD>
			<T>5K Beginning Run Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="This program is geared towards new runners who want to run a 5K successfully. The key is in the recipe that includes a perfect blend of easy running days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. The first five weeks or the program each have 3 run workouts and 2 cross-training workouts. Weeks 6-9 are the heaviest in volume, ramping up to 4 run workouts each. The Beginner 5K Program is geared to first-timer runners and gradually builds in mileage and intensity allowing your body to adapt to the new distances week to week. The program is a perfect strategy for those who have been running 2-3 times per week for 20-30 minutes. If you are running less, that is okay! Consider the 'Run-Walk' 5K Program and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from the best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals. ----------------Training Volume:"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\5K Run"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$24.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>This program is geared towards new runners who want to run a 5K successfully. The key is in the recipe that includes a perfect blend of easy running days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. The first five weeks or the program each have 3 run workouts and 2 cross-training workouts. Weeks 6-9 are the heaviest in volume, ramping up to 4 run workouts each. The Beginner 5K Program is geared to first-timer runners and gradually builds in mileage and intensity allowing your body to adapt to the new distances week to week. The program is a perfect strategy for those who have been running 2-3 times per week for 20-30 minutes. If you are running less, that is okay! Consider the 'Run-Walk' 5K Program and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from the best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals. ----------------Training Volume:</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="40">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=43</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=43</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=43</UD>
			<T>Beginning Olympic Distance Triathlon: 5.25 to 8 (or 10) hrs/wk - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="You might be a beginning triathlete or maybe you have a couple of races under your belt from previous seasons. In either case you are fit and are NOT a beginning athlete. Before beginning Week 1 of the plan you are capable of riding a bike 30 to 60 minutes two days a week and completing a long ride around two hours on a third day. You can swim 100 yards (or meters) nonstop and swimming for 30 minutes a couple of times per week is easy. You can run two days per week, one 30-minute run and a longer run of 45 minutes. Weekly training hours range from 5:15 to a maximum between 8:15 and 10:00. There is some flexibility built into the plan to accommodate individual differences. For example there is no time posted for the swim workouts. Obviously there can be big differences in swimming abilities between people with a competitive swim background and those just getting into swimming. Some of the run and bike workouts also have ranges built into the workouts. The plan has a general pattern of cycling and strength training on Monday and Wednesday, heading to only Mondays as the plan progresses. Strength training is optional in this plan. If you decide not to strength train, you can replace the strength training time with more time on the bike on those days. If you are currently strength training, you can keep your current routine. Be aware and notice if strength training is taking too much energy away from your swimming, cycling and running. If this is the case, consider reducing the exercises, sets or repetitions to allow higher quality workouts during the aerobic sessions. Swimming is shown on Tuesday, Thursday and some Saturdays. Running workouts are typically on Tuesday, some Thursdays and Saturdays. Long rides are on Sundays. Friday is always a day off. If it works better for you to have a different schedule and move the workouts around, it can be done. Try to keep similar workouts 48 hours apart. In other words, it is preferable to swim on Tuesday and Thursday instead of Tuesday and Wednesday. By Week 10 you are doing a training day that includes a morning swim followed by a 2:45 brick. The brick includes race-pace work. This plan is in the book, Triathlon Training Basics. --------------------Training volume:"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Olympic Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/GaleBernhardt.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$34.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>You might be a beginning triathlete or maybe you have a couple of races under your belt from previous seasons. In either case you are fit and are NOT a beginning athlete. Before beginning Week 1 of the plan you are capable of riding a bike 30 to 60 minutes two days a week and completing a long ride around two hours on a third day. You can swim 100 yards (or meters) nonstop and swimming for 30 minutes a couple of times per week is easy. You can run two days per week, one 30-minute run and a longer run of 45 minutes. Weekly training hours range from 5:15 to a maximum between 8:15 and 10:00. There is some flexibility built into the plan to accommodate individual differences. For example there is no time posted for the swim workouts. Obviously there can be big differences in swimming abilities between people with a competitive swim background and those just getting into swimming. Some of the run and bike workouts also have ranges built into the workouts. The plan has a general pattern of cycling and strength training on Monday and Wednesday, heading to only Mondays as the plan progresses. Strength training is optional in this plan. If you decide not to strength train, you can replace the strength training time with more time on the bike on those days. If you are currently strength training, you can keep your current routine. Be aware and notice if strength training is taking too much energy away from your swimming, cycling and running. If this is the case, consider reducing the exercises, sets or repetitions to allow higher quality workouts during the aerobic sessions. Swimming is shown on Tuesday, Thursday and some Saturdays. Running workouts are typically on Tuesday, some Thursdays and Saturdays. Long rides are on Sundays. Friday is always a day off. If it works better for you to have a different schedule and move the workouts around, it can be done. Try to keep similar workouts 48 hours apart. In other words, it is preferable to swim on Tuesday and Thursday instead of Tuesday and Wednesday. By Week 10 you are doing a training day that includes a morning swim followed by a 2:45 brick. The brick includes race-pace work. This plan is in the book, Triathlon Training Basics. --------------------Training volume:</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="41">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=2113</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=2113</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=2113</UD>
			<T>Beginning Half Marathon: 2.75 to 4.5 or 5.5 hrs/wk - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="This 14-week training plan is for the runner looking to step-up to a new distance and successfully complete a 13.1 mile event. Personal speed records will come at another race. The beginner plan is written for athletes intending to run, or run/walk, the event at a pace between 12-16 minutes per mile (finish time between 2:37-3:30). If you use the training plan 'as-is', it is a 14-week program. The first week of the plan has you running three or four days. One day is a 20-minute run, the second day is a 30-minute run, the third day is your 'long run' at 30-45 minutes and the optional fourth day is 20-minutes long. The plan helps you progress to a long run between 2:15-2:30 in Week 10.The plan is laid out with a form run on Tuesdays, an optional easy bike ride on Wednesdays, a race-pace or endurance run on Thursdays, a long run on Saturday and either a run or a long bike ride on Sunday. What? Why bike rides to prepare for a half-marathon?In coaching multi-sport athletes I found cycling can be effectively used to prepare people to run long distances without the joint-pounding stress that running creates. In the case you don't have a bike or don't want to use cycling to train for this event, there is a run scheduled in the plan for your to use on Sunday. So, all Wednesday bike rides are optional for everyone and the Sunday workout is a long bike or a run, not both.Training plan hours range from 2:45 to 4:30 (running only) to 5:30 (with cycling)."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Half Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/GaleBernhardt.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$34.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>This 14-week training plan is for the runner looking to step-up to a new distance and successfully complete a 13.1 mile event. Personal speed records will come at another race. The beginner plan is written for athletes intending to run, or run/walk, the event at a pace between 12-16 minutes per mile (finish time between 2:37-3:30). If you use the training plan 'as-is', it is a 14-week program. The first week of the plan has you running three or four days. One day is a 20-minute run, the second day is a 30-minute run, the third day is your 'long run' at 30-45 minutes and the optional fourth day is 20-minutes long. The plan helps you progress to a long run between 2:15-2:30 in Week 10.The plan is laid out with a form run on Tuesdays, an optional easy bike ride on Wednesdays, a race-pace or endurance run on Thursdays, a long run on Saturday and either a run or a long bike ride on Sunday. What? Why bike rides to prepare for a half-marathon?In coaching multi-sport athletes I found cycling can be effectively used to prepare people to run long distances without the joint-pounding stress that running creates. In the case you don't have a bike or don't want to use cycling to train for this event, there is a run scheduled in the plan for your to use on Sunday. So, all Wednesday bike rides are optional for everyone and the Sunday workout is a long bike or a run, not both.Training plan hours range from 2:45 to 4:30 (running only) to 5:30 (with cycling).</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="42">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=19</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=19</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=19</UD>
			<T>Walk-Run Marathon Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The Walk-Run Program is the perfect blend for walkers who want to challenge themselves by sprinkling in a little running or improve their finish times. It also works well for first-time marathoners who are new to running and want to safely progress to participating in the marathon. The blend of walking and running together reduces the overall impact and risk of injury, increases fun and enjoyment, and prepares you to go the distance.This program consists of workouts that include running for 1-2 minutes followed by walking 3-4 minutes. These walk-run intervals are repeated each session, allowing the body to cover the distance effectively and with reduced risk for injury. The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there. You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively. The Walk-Run Program is best suited for those who have been walking regularly 3-5 times per week for 45-80 minutes for at least six months. If you are currently walking less, that is okay! You may want to follow the Walk Marathon Program or the Walk-Run Half Marathon Program and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$39.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>The Walk-Run Program is the perfect blend for walkers who want to challenge themselves by sprinkling in a little running or improve their finish times. It also works well for first-time marathoners who are new to running and want to safely progress to participating in the marathon. The blend of walking and running together reduces the overall impact and risk of injury, increases fun and enjoyment, and prepares you to go the distance.This program consists of workouts that include running for 1-2 minutes followed by walking 3-4 minutes. These walk-run intervals are repeated each session, allowing the body to cover the distance effectively and with reduced risk for injury. The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there. You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively. The Walk-Run Program is best suited for those who have been walking regularly 3-5 times per week for 45-80 minutes for at least six months. If you are currently walking less, that is okay! You may want to follow the Walk Marathon Program or the Walk-Run Half Marathon Program and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="43">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=12</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=12</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=12</UD>
			<T>Intermediate Run Marathon Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The Intermediate Marathon Program is a step up in mileage and intensity from the Beginner Program and geared towards runners who have completed a marathon and want to improve their time. It incorporates two 20-mile runs instead of one, speed and race pace workouts, and more mileage. The Intermediate Marathon Program is best suited for those who have been running at least 4-5 times per week for 45-90 minutes for at least one year and have completed a marathon in the past year. If you are running less, it may be better strategy to start with the Beginner Marathon Program and build up to the Intermediate Marathon Program. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$39.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Intermediate"/>
			<S>The Intermediate Marathon Program is a step up in mileage and intensity from the Beginner Program and geared towards runners who have completed a marathon and want to improve their time. It incorporates two 20-mile runs instead of one, speed and race pace workouts, and more mileage. The Intermediate Marathon Program is best suited for those who have been running at least 4-5 times per week for 45-90 minutes for at least one year and have completed a marathon in the past year. If you are running less, it may be better strategy to start with the Beginner Marathon Program and build up to the Intermediate Marathon Program. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="44">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=60</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=60</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=60</UD>
			<T>Cyclist Base Training, Level 2: 5.45 to 9.5 hrs/wk - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="This 12-week plan is designed for an experienced and fit cyclist trying to keep good conditioning in the off-season. The athlete using this plan consistently rides a long ride each week, with or without a group. If you ride with a group, control the intensity as described in the plan. The long ride in the plan ranges between two and three hours. The length of this ride may be weather dependent. The athlete selecting this plan has had problems in the past trying to decide what to do in the off-season to maintain precious cycling fitness achieved during the summer season. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The plan is appropriate base training for road racers and mountain bike racers with goal events in the 2:00 to 3:00 range. It is also appropriate for cyclists that may not race, but want to ride fast in group rides or organized rides. (Century rides or multiday tours.) Before beginning this plan, you know your training zones described in the &quot;Intensity Document&quot; on my Biography page. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The training blocks are in three-week cycles to allow for good recovery. An aerobic time trial is included in the first week of the plan to help you monitor progress. Some of the workouts include a power option for athletes with access to power meters. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;Weekly training hours do not vary much throughout the program, but training intensity does. This is perfect for fit cyclists with limited training time or for those living in cold locations in the off-season. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The goals of this plan include: &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; Maintain a long ride of 2:00 to 3:00 hours throughout the plan. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; Reduce training in recovery weeks to 5:45 to absorb training. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; Keep training week hours at 8:00 to 9:30. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; Include a structured strength training program now, to improve cycling strength and speed after the 12-week plan is complete. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; Baseline test all-out time trial speed in Week 12 of the plan. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A; At the end of the plan be prepared to move to a build or pre-event training block."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Cycling Base"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/GaleBernhardt.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$34.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Intermediate"/>
			<S>This 12-week plan is designed for an experienced and fit cyclist trying to keep good conditioning in the off-season. The athlete using this plan consistently rides a long ride each week, with or without a group. If you ride with a group, control the intensity as described in the plan. The long ride in the plan ranges between two and three hours. The length of this ride may be weather dependent. The athlete selecting this plan has had problems in the past trying to decide what to do in the off-season to maintain precious cycling fitness achieved during the summer season. 

The plan is appropriate base training for road racers and mountain bike racers with goal events in the 2:00 to 3:00 range. It is also appropriate for cyclists that may not race, but want to ride fast in group rides or organized rides. (Century rides or multiday tours.) Before beginning this plan, you know your training zones described in the "Intensity Document" on my Biography page. 

The training blocks are in three-week cycles to allow for good recovery. An aerobic time trial is included in the first week of the plan to help you monitor progress. Some of the workouts include a power option for athletes with access to power meters. 

Weekly training hours do not vary much throughout the program, but training intensity does. This is perfect for fit cyclists with limited training time or for those living in cold locations in the off-season. 

The goals of this plan include: 



 Maintain a long ride of 2:00 to 3:00 hours throughout the plan. 

 Reduce training in recovery weeks to 5:45 to absorb training. 

 Keep training week hours at 8:00 to 9:30. 

 Include a structured strength training program now, to improve cycling strength and speed after the 12-week plan is complete. 

 Baseline test all-out time trial speed in Week 12 of the plan. 

 At the end of the plan be prepared to move to a build or pre-event training block.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="45">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=17</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=17</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=17</UD>
			<T>Beginning Run Marathon Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="If this is your first marathon and you have been running regularly, this is the program for you! It will take you from a 5 mile run at the end of week one and gradually progress to a peak 20 mile run in week 17 of the program. The key is in the recipe that includes a blend of easy running days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. The best strategy for finding the right program is to select one that most closely matches your current training volume as a starting point. The Beginner or First-Timer Marathon Program is designed for those who have been running between 3-5 miles comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months. If you are running less, consider the 'Run-Walk' Program for the Marathon or the Beginner Run Program for the Half Marathon and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated during training."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$39.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>If this is your first marathon and you have been running regularly, this is the program for you! It will take you from a 5 mile run at the end of week one and gradually progress to a peak 20 mile run in week 17 of the program. The key is in the recipe that includes a blend of easy running days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. The best strategy for finding the right program is to select one that most closely matches your current training volume as a starting point. The Beginner or First-Timer Marathon Program is designed for those who have been running between 3-5 miles comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months. If you are running less, consider the 'Run-Walk' Program for the Marathon or the Beginner Run Program for the Half Marathon and build your way up. In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John 'the Penguin' Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated during training.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="46">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=10</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=10</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=10</UD>
			<T>Beginning Run Half Marathon Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="If this is your first half marathon and you want to train to run the half marathon, this is the program for you!  It will take you from a 4 mile run to the start line and finish line of the half marathon.  Week by week, you will gradually progress your mileage to running 10 miles in preparation for the race.  The key is in the recipe that includes a perfect blend of running easy days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The Beginner Program is geared to first-timer half marathoners and gradually builds in mileage and intensity allowing your body to adapt to the new distances week to week. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there.  You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively.  &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The Beginner Half Marathon Program is a perfect strategy for those who have been running 30-50 minutes comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months.  If you are running less, that is okay!  Consider the &quot;Run-Walk&quot; Program for the half marathon or 10K Run Program and build your way up. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John &quot;the Penguin&quot; Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Half Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$29.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>If this is your first half marathon and you want to train to run the half marathon, this is the program for you!  It will take you from a 4 mile run to the start line and finish line of the half marathon.  Week by week, you will gradually progress your mileage to running 10 miles in preparation for the race.  The key is in the recipe that includes a perfect blend of running easy days, long endurance runs, cross-training and rest. 



The Beginner Program is geared to first-timer half marathoners and gradually builds in mileage and intensity allowing your body to adapt to the new distances week to week. 



The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there.  You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively.  



The Beginner Half Marathon Program is a perfect strategy for those who have been running 30-50 minutes comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months.  If you are running less, that is okay!  Consider the "Run-Walk" Program for the half marathon or 10K Run Program and build your way up. 



In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John "the Penguin" Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="47">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=151</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=151</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=151</UD>
			<T>Core Training for a Running (Intermediate) - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Core Training is vital to your athletic success and peak performance. The movements in this 15-minute program are designed to stabilize and strengthen your skeletal structure. Your core muscles act to synergize your abdominals, upper and lower back, hips, gluteus, and thigh areas. You can't have effective transfer of energy or power without a strong core. As you begin to work and condition the core, you will notice less fatigue associated with the body breaking down, helping to increase strength and reduce the risk of injury. As you prepare for your marathon, the secret will be the effective transfer of energy from your core to your legs through what we call functional movements. To improve your running stamina and endurance, we're going to increase your running strength through a series of running specific exercises and movements. Remember, you are only as stung as your weakest link! Core Training for runners can be a great addition to your current strength-training program. This 4-week Intermediate Core Training Plan is designed for the seasoned individual getting back into fitness. It will refresh you on all the current core training exercises used to strengthen your abdomen and lower back (core). This 15 minute training plan would be a great addition to your current strength-training program."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/MaryNevers.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$9.99"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Intermediate"/>
			<S>Core Training is vital to your athletic success and peak performance. The movements in this 15-minute program are designed to stabilize and strengthen your skeletal structure. Your core muscles act to synergize your abdominals, upper and lower back, hips, gluteus, and thigh areas. You can't have effective transfer of energy or power without a strong core. As you begin to work and condition the core, you will notice less fatigue associated with the body breaking down, helping to increase strength and reduce the risk of injury. As you prepare for your marathon, the secret will be the effective transfer of energy from your core to your legs through what we call functional movements. To improve your running stamina and endurance, we're going to increase your running strength through a series of running specific exercises and movements. Remember, you are only as stung as your weakest link! Core Training for runners can be a great addition to your current strength-training program. This 4-week Intermediate Core Training Plan is designed for the seasoned individual getting back into fitness. It will refresh you on all the current core training exercises used to strengthen your abdomen and lower back (core). This 15 minute training plan would be a great addition to your current strength-training program.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="48">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=6</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=6</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=6</UD>
			<T>Beginner Olympic Distance Tri Program: 2.75 to 7 hrs/wk - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="While it's nice to make your triathlon debut at a sprint-distance event, it's not always convenient or possible. For example, a nearby town or city might host a great Olympic-distance race and the date of the event fits nicely into your busy calendar. Although the event sounds like a lot of fun you wonder, 'Do I have the time to train for that event? Can I really complete an Olympic-distance race or am I fooling myself?' It doesn't take as much time to train for an Olympic-distance event as you might think. With a solid training plan, you can successfully complete the event. This 12-Week training plan is for beginning triathletes looking to comfortably complete their first Olympic distance event (0.9 miles of swimming, 24.8 miles of cycling and 6.2 miles of running.) The athlete using this program can currently swim 50 meters without stopping and ride an indoor or outdoor bike for 30 to 60 minutes. There are currently two options included within this plan for the running portion ? a run description and a description for a combination of running and walking. The largest week of training volume is approximately 7:00. This volume of training can easily fit into the busiest of schedules. This training plan originally appeared in the February through April 2002 issues of 'Triathlete' magazine.--------------------Training volume:"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Olympic Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/GaleBernhardt.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$34.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>While it's nice to make your triathlon debut at a sprint-distance event, it's not always convenient or possible. For example, a nearby town or city might host a great Olympic-distance race and the date of the event fits nicely into your busy calendar. Although the event sounds like a lot of fun you wonder, 'Do I have the time to train for that event? Can I really complete an Olympic-distance race or am I fooling myself?' It doesn't take as much time to train for an Olympic-distance event as you might think. With a solid training plan, you can successfully complete the event. This 12-Week training plan is for beginning triathletes looking to comfortably complete their first Olympic distance event (0.9 miles of swimming, 24.8 miles of cycling and 6.2 miles of running.) The athlete using this program can currently swim 50 meters without stopping and ride an indoor or outdoor bike for 30 to 60 minutes. There are currently two options included within this plan for the running portion ? a run description and a description for a combination of running and walking. The largest week of training volume is approximately 7:00. This volume of training can easily fit into the busiest of schedules. This training plan originally appeared in the February through April 2002 issues of 'Triathlete' magazine.--------------------Training volume:</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="49">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=21</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=21</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=21</UD>
			<T>Run-Walk Half Marathon Training Program - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The Run-Walk Half Marathon Program is a very popular program for first-timers and those who want to enjoy training with minimal risk of injury.  The program includes running mixed with power-walk breaks.  It is the recipe of the number of minutes if each that transforms every day mortals to half marathoners.  This is also the Penguin�s favorite plan.  He always uses some blend of running and walking in training and racing. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The Run-Walk Program is a perfect program for first-timers, those who have had problems with aches or pains and those who want to progress safely with reduced risk of injury and get in great shape while training for the race. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The blend of walking and running together reduces the overall impact and risk of injury, increases the fun factor and enjoyment and prepares you to go the distance. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there.  You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively.&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;The &quot;Run-Walk&quot; Program is best suited for those who are new to running and have been covering at least 30 minutes comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months. If you are currently running less, that is okay!  You may want to follow the Walk-Run Half Marathon Program or the Run-Walk 10K Program and build your way up. &amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;&amp;#0A;In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John &quot;the Penguin&quot; Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan\Half Marathon"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/JennyHadfield.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$29.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Beginner"/>
			<S>The Run-Walk Half Marathon Program is a very popular program for first-timers and those who want to enjoy training with minimal risk of injury.  The program includes running mixed with power-walk breaks.  It is the recipe of the number of minutes if each that transforms every day mortals to half marathoners.  This is also the Penguin�s favorite plan.  He always uses some blend of running and walking in training and racing. 



The Run-Walk Program is a perfect program for first-timers, those who have had problems with aches or pains and those who want to progress safely with reduced risk of injury and get in great shape while training for the race. 



The blend of walking and running together reduces the overall impact and risk of injury, increases the fun factor and enjoyment and prepares you to go the distance. 



The key is to find the program that best matches your current training and start there.  You will progress more quickly and reach your goals more effectively.



The "Run-Walk" Program is best suited for those who are new to running and have been covering at least 30 minutes comfortably 3-4 times per week for at least six months. If you are currently running less, that is okay!  You may want to follow the Walk-Run Half Marathon Program or the Run-Walk 10K Program and build your way up. 



In addition to the daily training schedule, this program contains weekly inspirational messages from best-selling author and Runner's World columnist John "the Penguin" Bingham. His words will help you stay motivated so that you can achieve your goals.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="50">
			<U>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=366</U>
			<UE>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=366</UE>
			<UD>http://training.active.com/TransactionManager/viewPlan.do?tpId=366</UD>
			<T>TRX Pre-Habilitation Training for Triathletes (3 days/wk) - Active Trainer</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="TRX Pre-Habilitation for Triathletes is a pro-active program that will correct the muscular imbalances and reduce the potential for overuse injuries that result from the repetitive nature of triathlon training.This 9 week program consists of a 12 exercise progression that includes 4 movements for each of the lower body, upper body and core. Every exercise has been carefully selected specifically as part of this preventative program.The program is based on timed sets as opposed to target repetitions. The goal is to complete as many repetitions with good form in the allotted time as possible. As skill and fitness increases, you will be able to complete more repetitions in the time allowed.he program gives the option of being done as a complete progression or broken up into 3 short sections of 4 exercises, depending on available time.  *This program requires that you have the use of a TRX Suspension Trainer. For more information on the TRX visit www.fitnessanywhere.com/multisports"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Products"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Triathlon"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="active trainer training plan program coaching personal calendar fitness core"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Training Plan"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/training_plan_icon.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/activeTrainer/FraserQuelch.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationCost" V="$19.95"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Intermediate"/>
			<S>TRX Pre-Habilitation for Triathletes is a pro-active program that will correct the muscular imbalances and reduce the potential for overuse injuries that result from the repetitive nature of triathlon training.This 9 week program consists of a 12 exercise progression that includes 4 movements for each of the lower body, upper body and core. Every exercise has been carefully selected specifically as part of this preventative program.The program is based on timed sets as opposed to target repetitions. The goal is to complete as many repetitions with good form in the allotted time as possible. As skill and fitness increases, you will be able to complete more repetitions in the time allowed.he program gives the option of being done as a complete progression or broken up into 3 short sections of 4 exercises, depending on available time.  *This program requires that you have the use of a TRX Suspension Trainer. For more information on the TRX visit www.fitnessanywhere.com/multisports</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
		<R N="51">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=D3D064D4-9901-4838-9F8F-002B2C1F5B9B</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=D3D064D4-9901-4838-9F8F-002B2C1F5B9B</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=D3D064D4-9901-4838-9F8F-002B2C1F5B9B</UD>
			<T>LA Leggers</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club"/>
			<MT N="address" V="P.O. Box 761"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Santa Monica"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90406"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="52">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=24680A1F-6546-41CE-880E-01B895545AE2</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=24680A1F-6546-41CE-880E-01B895545AE2</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=24680A1F-6546-41CE-880E-01B895545AE2</UD>
			<T>Stoner Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Basketball"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="League"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90001"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="53">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=117D9E70-66A8-4258-AD7A-03075DA942CF</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=117D9E70-66A8-4258-AD7A-03075DA942CF</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=117D9E70-66A8-4258-AD7A-03075DA942CF</UD>
			<T>Los Angeles Field Hockey Association</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Field Hockey"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Athletic Association"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90001"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="54">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F875D110-E393-4680-B851-055D3F58E104</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F875D110-E393-4680-B851-055D3F58E104</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=F875D110-E393-4680-B851-055D3F58E104</UD>
			<T>Panorama Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Basketball"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="League"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Panorama City"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91402"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="55">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=886C2BA6-36A0-4531-BAFD-07CA2AF4E85D</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=886C2BA6-36A0-4531-BAFD-07CA2AF4E85D</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=886C2BA6-36A0-4531-BAFD-07CA2AF4E85D</UD>
			<T>Westwood Recreation Center</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Basketball"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="League"/>
			<MT N="address" V="1350 Sepulveda Boulevard"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90025"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="56">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=5946A0B0-F995-40E2-BA89-0823D540437A</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=5946A0B0-F995-40E2-BA89-0823D540437A</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=5946A0B0-F995-40E2-BA89-0823D540437A</UD>
			<T>Culver City Hockey League</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Ice Hockey"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="League"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Culver City"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90230"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="57">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=006F3375-E63C-4C3C-8197-0ABD059A572C</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=006F3375-E63C-4C3C-8197-0ABD059A572C</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=006F3375-E63C-4C3C-8197-0ABD059A572C</UD>
			<T>Santa Monica Windjammers Yacht Club</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Sailing"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club"/>
			<MT N="address" V="13589 Mindanao Way"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Marina del Rey"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90292"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="58">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=AD9D08E0-4FA4-442B-8274-0D2AFD071D3C</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=AD9D08E0-4FA4-442B-8274-0D2AFD071D3C</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=AD9D08E0-4FA4-442B-8274-0D2AFD071D3C</UD>
			<T>Edelweiss Ski and Sport Club</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Skiing"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club"/>
			<MT N="address" V="P.O. Box 2715"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Van Nuys"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91404"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="59">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=C4777E61-5C74-48E1-90A7-1260BED94AA6</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=C4777E61-5C74-48E1-90A7-1260BED94AA6</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=C4777E61-5C74-48E1-90A7-1260BED94AA6</UD>
			<T>Panorama City Women's Ice Hockey League</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Ice Hockey"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="League"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Panorama City"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91402"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="60">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4C8CAF0E-D36A-4F87-AA52-160618C5C3CE</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4C8CAF0E-D36A-4F87-AA52-160618C5C3CE</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=4C8CAF0E-D36A-4F87-AA52-160618C5C3CE</UD>
			<T>Pacific Singlehanded Sailing Association</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Sailing"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Athletic Association"/>
			<MT N="address" V="P.O. Box 9523"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Marina Del Rey"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90295"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="61">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A74A33B6-33CF-479E-8D5C-17D04FBCB97E</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A74A33B6-33CF-479E-8D5C-17D04FBCB97E</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=A74A33B6-33CF-479E-8D5C-17D04FBCB97E</UD>
			<T>Sunshine Volleyball Club</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Volleyball"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club"/>
			<MT N="address" V="12021 Wilshire Blvd #622"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90025"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="62">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9E5E930A-5A65-4A5A-B57A-1A220CBC7125</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9E5E930A-5A65-4A5A-B57A-1A220CBC7125</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Active_CRM_details.htm?assetId=9E5E930A-5A65-4A5A-B57A-1A220CBC7125</UD>
			<T>California's Complete Sports Club</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Organizations"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Skiing"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Club"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90024"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
		<R N="63">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1588276&amp;assetId=e226a0ae-fec7-4055-9b1b-000102f8020a</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1588276&amp;assetId=e226a0ae-fec7-4055-9b1b-000102f8020a</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1588276&amp;assetId=e226a0ae-fec7-4055-9b1b-000102f8020a</UD>
			<T>Aspen Summer Race Series</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Either Register for the Aspen Downtown Mile or the Aspen Summer Race Series including the Aspen Mountain Uphill Event #2, and the Chuck Severy 5K Event #3.Aspen Downtown Mile – Event #1 of Aspen Summer Race Series.   One mile race within the Aspen city limits.   Benefits Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Pre-register at Ute Mountaineer by 5 pm 6/23 or race day registration 7:00 a.m. at Paepcke.   Start 8:00 a.m.Aspen Mountain Uphill -  Event #2 of Aspen Summer Race Series.   4.4 mile, 3400 vertical run and Mtn. bike race form the base to the top of Ajax on the summer road.   Benefit for the Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Race Day Registration 7:00 a.m.   Start: Bikers 8:00 a.m., Walkers/Runners 8:15 a.m.Chuck Severy 5K – Event #3 of Aspen Summer Race Summer Series.   Benefit for Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Pre-register at Ute by 5:00 p.m. 10/6 or race day registration."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Event"/>
			<MT N="address" V="Garmish and Hopkins Street"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Aspen"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Colorado"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="81621"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="festu@rof.net"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="970-927-0265"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-06-07"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="All"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="false"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S>Either Register for the Aspen Downtown Mile or the Aspen Summer Race Series including the Aspen Mountain Uphill Event #2, and the Chuck Severy 5K Event #3.Aspen Downtown Mile – Event #1 of Aspen Summer Race Series.   One mile race within the Aspen city limits.   Benefits Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Pre-register at Ute Mountaineer by 5 pm 6/23 or race day registration 7:00 a.m. at Paepcke.   Start 8:00 a.m.Aspen Mountain Uphill -  Event #2 of Aspen Summer Race Series.   4.4 mile, 3400 vertical run and Mtn. bike race form the base to the top of Ajax on the summer road.   Benefit for the Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Race Day Registration 7:00 a.m.   Start: Bikers 8:00 a.m., Walkers/Runners 8:15 a.m.Chuck Severy 5K – Event #3 of Aspen Summer Race Summer Series.   Benefit for Aspen HS Cross Country Team.   Pre-register at Ute by 5:00 p.m. 10/6 or race day registration.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="64">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1532479&amp;assetId=d278a9c9-ca71-4105-aa2c-000112f1f6f8</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1532479&amp;assetId=d278a9c9-ca71-4105-aa2c-000112f1f6f8</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1532479&amp;assetId=d278a9c9-ca71-4105-aa2c-000112f1f6f8</UD>
			<T>Charlie Wallace Memorial 5K Race</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Event"/>
			<MT N="address" V="Rhododendron Road"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Fitzwilliam"/>
			<MT N="state" V="New Hampshire"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="03447"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="fitzwilliamrec@ptcnh.net"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="603-585-7270"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-06-07"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Family"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="false"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="65">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/smithtown/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=194</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/smithtown/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=194</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/smithtown/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=194</UD>
			<T>Level 2 Swim: Fund  Aquatic Skills, Session  2C #660202.103</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="If you are unsure of your child's level, please sign up for the lower level. Each child will be individually tested and moved to the appropriate level. Repetition of various levels is not uncommon and is often suggested. This is especially true for youngsters who only swim in warm weather and outdoor pools. Parents are cautioned against registering a child for too high a level.&amp;#0A;Maturity, physical strength and mastery of basic skills are considerations. The daily schedule of lessons, which run Mon - Fri, is designed to&amp;#0A;accommodate the optimum number of children. Our classes are 50 minutes, and we have three daily class times."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Smithtown"/>
			<MT N="state" V="NY"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="11787"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-07-28"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="66">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/roanokerec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=1805</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/roanokerec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=1805</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/roanokerec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=1805</UD>
			<T>Swim Lessons 4 - Level 2 #3322.417</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The purpose is to give students success with fundamental skills.  Children age 4 to 9 will learn: Moving in the water while wearing a life jacket ? Recognizing a swimmer in distress and getting help ? Submerging entire head ? Bobbing in water ? Front and back glide ? Jellyfish float ? Treading water using arm and leg motions ? Swimming using combined stoke on front and back."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Roanoke"/>
			<MT N="state" V="TX"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="76262"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-08-04"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="67">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1573924&amp;assetId=21f55b7b-61ea-42c4-840c-0004c73d0ca1</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1573924&amp;assetId=21f55b7b-61ea-42c4-840c-0004c73d0ca1</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1573924&amp;assetId=21f55b7b-61ea-42c4-840c-0004c73d0ca1</UD>
			<T>Lauren's Run for a Reason, Benefiting the Sudden Unexplained Death in Children Program</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="5K Run to start at 10:00 AM2K Walk to start at 10:15 AM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Event"/>
			<MT N="address" V="13080 Territorial Road"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Maple Grove"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Minnesota"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="55369"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="strymucha@yahoo.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="763-757-8841"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-08-10"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/upimages/LaurensRun.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Family"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S>5K Run to start at 10:00 AM2K Walk to start at 10:15 AM</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="68">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1587849&amp;assetId=4e7ddcd5-77d0-4417-8122-00050bb891f5</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1587849&amp;assetId=4e7ddcd5-77d0-4417-8122-00050bb891f5</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1587849&amp;assetId=4e7ddcd5-77d0-4417-8122-00050bb891f5</UD>
			<T>Sizzlin' Summer Classic 2008 5K Run/Walk</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Event"/>
			<MT N="address" V="2325 Chester Blvd"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Richmond"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Indiana"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="47374"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="karlstev@indiana.edu"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="765-973-8240"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-07-12"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Family"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="false"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="69">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1516457&amp;assetId=32cede89-2ae5-4a3b-855a-00083acdbb4d</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1516457&amp;assetId=32cede89-2ae5-4a3b-855a-00083acdbb4d</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1516457&amp;assetId=32cede89-2ae5-4a3b-855a-00083acdbb4d</UD>
			<T>Varina Youth Sports Spring 2008</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="REGISTRATION REMAins open for BABE RUTH (13-15) and Senior Babe Ruth (16 - 18) Baseball AND 18U Fastpitch (17-18) Softball.  Join now!"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Baseball"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Tournament"/>
			<MT N="address" V="7200 Dorey Park Drive"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Richmond"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Virginia"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="23231"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="dave@conquestgroup.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="804-358-0560"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-04-01"/>
			<MT N="endDate" V="2008-06-15"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/upimages/VYS New Logo-small7.jpg"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Youth"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="false"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S>REGISTRATION REMAins open for BABE RUTH (13-15) and Senior Babe Ruth (16 - 18) Baseball AND 18U Fastpitch (17-18) Softball.  Join now!</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="70">
			<U>http://www.active.com/tennis/USTA_Event_Tournaments.htm?EventID=62605</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/tennis/USTA_Event_Tournaments.htm?EventID=62605</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/tennis/USTA_Event_Tournaments.htm?EventID=62605</UD>
			<T> 3rd Metro Area Junior Open L3</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Location: Jefferson Junior T A, Division: BG(18-10)s,FIC, FIC, Notes: Rain date 8/11.  Awards 1-5.  **FOR DIRECTIONS TO TENNIS SITE USE JEFFERSON HIGH SCHOOL,   4141 FLOW"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Tennis"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Tournament"/>
			<MT N="address" V="Jefferson Junior T A, Attn: G H Edwards, Jefferson High School"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Charles Town"/>
			<MT N="state" V="WV"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="25414"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="(304) 725-7929"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-08-08"/>
			<MT N="endDate" V="2008-08-10"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://tennislink.usta.com/tournaments/images/USTA_logo_small.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Junior"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S>USTA - Boys' 18 Singles, Boys' 16 Singles, Boys' 14 Singles, Boys' 12 Singles, Boys' 10 Singles, Girls' 18 Singles, Girls' 16 Singles, Girls' 14 Singles, Girls' 12 Singles, Girls' 10 Singles</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="71">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/grantrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=713</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/grantrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=713</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/grantrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=713</UD>
			<T>Wood Crafts P-2nd #2235.204</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Do you like to paint on wood? We have lots of projects that can be painted and left out through out the year or at certain holidays."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Ulysses"/>
			<MT N="state" V="KS"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="67880"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-07-03"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="72">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/wecmrd/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=2191</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/wecmrd/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=2191</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/wecmrd/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=2191</UD>
			<T>Private Swim Lesson 2 pak, (1B) Sat 9am #8869.214</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Private Swim Lessons are designed to allow personal attention and tailor skills to swimmer's level and ability."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Gypsum"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CO"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="81637"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-06-14"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="73">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/oaklandpark/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=36</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/oaklandpark/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=36</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/oaklandpark/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=36</UD>
			<T>Boys Ages 10-12 #77</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Oakland Park"/>
			<MT N="state" V="FL"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="33334"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-06-02"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="74">
			<U>http://activenet.active.com/onalaskaparkrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=859</U>
			<UE>http://activenet.active.com/onalaskaparkrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=859</UE>
			<UD>http://activenet.active.com/onalaskaparkrec/registrationmain.sdi?source=showAsset.sdi&amp;activity_id=859</UD>
			<T>Boating Safety #1502.101</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The Onalaska Park and Rec and DNR will be offering a boating safety course this summer.  The course consists of a basic eight hours of classroom instruction in the principles of boating safety. Wisconsin boating safety certification is required for operators born on or after Jan. 1, 1989 and at least 16 years of age. Operators 12-15 must either have a certificate or have an adult on board while operating. Anyone 10 or older is eligible to take the class and receive certification. Certificates do not become valid until participant reaches 12."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Community Services"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Class"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Onalaska"/>
			<MT N="state" V="WI"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="54650"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-06-23"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="75">
			<U>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1524528&amp;assetId=80489476-2ad9-4e7b-ba8e-000df947fde9</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1524528&amp;assetId=80489476-2ad9-4e7b-ba8e-000df947fde9</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/page/Event_Details.htm?event_id=1524528&amp;assetId=80489476-2ad9-4e7b-ba8e-000df947fde9</UD>
			<T>George Mason Softball Clinic</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="George Mason Softball ClinicSunday February 10, 2008Grades 2-5 12-2pmGrades 6-8 2-4pmCost: $15Location:  Camps will be held at the GMU Field house located on the corner of 123 and University Dr.Registration:  Check in will be held at the Fieldhouse 30 minutes prior to camp for every session.Inclement Weather:  703-993-3813 Snow Line.  Camp cancellations will be made up the first available time for the indoor facility.For questions concerning camps please contact Erica Ayers at 703-993-3813 or via e-mail at eayers@gmu.eduRefund Policy: Camp refunds must be submitted in writing."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Activities"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Softball\Fast Pitch"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Camp"/>
			<MT N="address" V="4400 University Dr."/>
			<MT N="city" V="Fairfax"/>
			<MT N="state" V="Virginia"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="22030"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="eayers@gmu.edu"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="703-993-3813"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-02-10"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://www.active.com/images/events/hotrace.gif"/>
			<MT N="onlineRegistrationAvailable" V="true"/>
			<MT N="participationCriteria" V="Youth"/>
			<MT N="onlineDonationAvailable" V="false"/>
			<MT N="onlineMembershipAvailable" V="false"/>
			<S>George Mason Softball ClinicSunday February 10, 2008Grades 2-5 12-2pmGrades 6-8 2-4pmCost: $15Location:  Camps will be held at the GMU Field house located on the corner of 123 and University Dr.Registration:  Check in will be held at the Fieldhouse 30 minutes prior to camp for every session.Inclement Weather:  703-993-3813 Snow Line.  Camp cancellations will be made up the first available time for the indoor facility.For questions concerning camps please contact Erica Ayers at 703-993-3813 or via e-mail at eayers@gmu.eduRefund Policy: Camp refunds must be submitted in writing.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
		<R N="76">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Glendale-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Glendale-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Glendale-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UD>
			<T>Brad H. (Piano Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="&quot;I will do my best ... in what I do best ... to do what's best ... for you or your child.&quot;"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="piano, music, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Glendale"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91205"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/136635_1203545779_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>&amp;nbsp;     I am a young, energetic, friendly, passionate, professional, classically trained musician. I love life, I love music, and I love teaching! I say that first, because my credentials would be pretty meaningless if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a nice guy who loves his job.&amp;nbsp;     With that in mind, here is my teaching philosophy, including&amp;nbsp;what you can expect from me as a teacher and as a person:     MY PHILOSOPHY      I&amp;nbsp;believe that every child is precious (every adult too, for that...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="77">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/elliebunker?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/elliebunker?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/elliebunker?s=active</UD>
			<T>Ellie Bunker (Violin Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Musical Director of Flintridge Sacred Heart Academy in La Canada, Flintridge"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="violin, music, viola, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Glendale"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91205"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/1551_1_PIC_0040_tn.JPG"/>
			<S>I am British, now living in Glendale with my husband. As well as teaching I also have a busy performing schedule and perform regularly with my husband who is a guitarist, as a duo, for weddings/parties/other events.   I teach people of all ages and abilities. I teach classical music, traditional note reading and technique.    2006 - ongoing  Musical Director for FSHA, La Canada, Flintridge.     2005 - 2006  Southern California Music School, Riverside, CA Teacher of Violin, Viola and Piano...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="78">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/hollywoodpopacademy?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/hollywoodpopacademy?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/hollywoodpopacademy?s=active</UD>
			<T>Hollywood Pop Academy (Singing Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="the #1 artist development facility for aspiring singers"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="singing, voice, songwriting, music, music performance, dance"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90028"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/prov_61192_3923_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>Our definition of success begins and ends with the impact we have on you.     “WHO’S NEXT IN POP?”  HOLLYWOOD POP ACADEMY MAKES STARS SHINE    Hollywood Pop Academy (HPA) is Los Angeles’ #1 professional training facility for aspiring singers ages 7-30.  HPA is the top forum for young talent to get exposure to the music industry's leading decision makers, talent scouts and A&amp;R executives.  Located in the renowned Kodak Theatre complex, HPA has groomed three American Idol Top-Ten...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="79">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/MB?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/MB?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/MB?s=active</UD>
			<T>Marty Buttwinick (Songwriting Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Personalized Music Lessons at the Buttwinick Teaching Studio"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="songwriting, music, music performance, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Glendale"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91205"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/34608_7330_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>Hello! Ive been teaching privately for over twenty-five years and have guided more than 800 students in achieving their musical goals. My background includes formal university training and world class private instruction, as well as being a professional musician for thirty-five years.     In addition to teaching beginning and intermediate students, some top acts that my professional students have performed or recorded with include Chaka Khan, Isaac Hayes, MC Lyte, Taylor Dane and Doug E....</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="80">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons5?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons5?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons5?s=active</UD>
			<T>William A. (Guitar Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="I love to teach and show people that anyone has the ability to make a masterpiece!"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="guitar, music, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90028"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/140261_10003_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>William:     - Started playing guitar age 12     - Began private lessons age 14     - Won numerous guitar dueling battles     - Began giving private lessons as a way to help expand the horizons of kids wanting to learn and myself     - Toured extensively in Japan with Heinous Criminal 03'-05'     - Enrolled at Musician's Institute Winter 07'     &amp;nbsp;     Music is my passion and being able to convey my ideas and thoughts to another musician clearly is something I strive for in my daily life. I...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="81">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-guitar-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-guitar-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-guitar-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</UD>
			<T>Enrique S. (Guitar Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Music lessons from an instructor with a love for Rock Music!"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="guitar, music, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90028"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/138977_1207152612_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>My name is Enrique; I was born and raised in South America. I have always liked music but after listening bands like Korn and Slipknot I decided that I wanted to play Music, the instrument would be a drum kit. After begging for a drum kit, I got a guitar instead so I began playing guitar at the age of 15. The first years of my guitar playing were self taught.     &amp;nbsp;     After graduating from High School I came to the US to learn English, but instead I spent most of the time playing guitar...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="82">
			<U>http://www.activegolf.com/instructor.aspx?id=6689</U>
			<UE>http://www.activegolf.com/instructor.aspx?id=6689</UE>
			<UD>http://www.activegolf.com/instructor.aspx?id=6689</UD>
			<T>Bob O</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Golf"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Golf Instructor"/>
			<MT N="address" V="6550 Odessa Ave"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Van Nuys"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91406"/>
			<MT N="country" V="USA"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="rto@rtolaw.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="818-781-4636"/>
			<S/>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="83">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/AaronMcClaskey?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/AaronMcClaskey?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/AaronMcClaskey?s=active</UD>
			<T>Aaron McClaskey (Piano Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Classical and Jazz Piano lessons with concert artist, Aaron McClaskey"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="piano, music, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90089"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/137623_9193_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>&amp;nbsp;     MM: USC Thornton School of Music, full scholarship     DMA:&amp;nbsp; USC Thornton School of Music, teaching fellow     Assistant Lecturer, USC Thornton School of Music     Teaching assistant to John Perry     "Teacher of the Year", USU Youth Conservatory     Classical and Jazz Keyboard instructor, Bethesda University     I began lessons at the age of 5, and decided at the age of 10 that I wanted to make music for the rest of my life.&amp;nbsp; I started teaching at age 14, while at the same...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="84">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Northridge-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Northridge-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Northridge-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UD>
			<T>Hay-Ling T. (Piano Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="piano, music, guitar, music performance, organ, music theory"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="piano, music, guitar, music performance, organ, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Northridge"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91325"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/139492_1208596623_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>&amp;nbsp;At age 17, Hay- Ling was a piano accompanist and piano/music  tutor at Modesto Junior College Music Department, where she also became a  teacher assistant later.     &amp;nbsp;Hay  Ling&amp;rsquo;s early musical training came primarily from Ms. Grace Janice Tseng who is  an honor graduate of The Royal Schools of Music, London  and prizes winner of various piano competitions in Hong   Kong. At age 16, Hay Ling earned her Certificate of Merit in Grade  8 Piano from the Associated Board of the Royal...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="85">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/North-Hollywood-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/North-Hollywood-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/North-Hollywood-music-theory-piano-lessons?s=active</UD>
			<T>Claire H. (Piano Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Music and Piano lessons from a Berklee graduate!"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="piano, music, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="North Hollywood"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="91605"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/139621_9920_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>I start taking classical piano lessons since I was 7. I am classical trained and also play other contemporary styles such as R&amp;amp;B, Jazz, Pop, Funk, Blues, Soul and Latin music.      My major in Musician&amp;rsquo;s Institute is keyboard performance where I have learned different styles of playing and performing. After graduated from M.I. I moved to Boston to attend Beklee College of Music. My major was performance and writing.</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="86">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-lessons1?s=active</UD>
			<T>Kent  S. (Guitar Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Learn music through popular genres!"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="guitar, music, singing, voice, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90028"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/138945_1207709054_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>&amp;nbsp;     I began playing guitar at age 15, taking inspiration from bands such as Nirvana, Iron Maiden, and Metallica. &amp;nbsp;Throughout high school, I fronted a popular rock/metal/funk band (sounds crazy, right?) taking on guitar, vocal, and songwriting responsibilities, so I know what it takes to bring a show together. &amp;nbsp;After gigging central PA, I moved out to further my studies at Musicians Institute, located in Hollywood, CA. &amp;nbsp;Since my time in LA, I have worked with various...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="87">
			<U>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons7?s=active</U>
			<UE>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons7?s=active</UE>
			<UD>http://takelessons.com/Los-Angeles-music-theory-guitar-lessons7?s=active</UD>
			<T>Kenneth W. (Guitar Lessons)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="guitar, music, drums, bass guitar, music recording, music theory"/>
			<MT N="category" V="People"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Music"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="guitar, music, drums, bass guitar, music recording, music theory"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Trainer &amp; Instructors"/>
			<MT N="city" V="Los Angeles"/>
			<MT N="state" V="CA"/>
			<MT N="zip" V="90019"/>
			<MT N="country" V="United States"/>
			<MT N="contactEmail" V="teacher@takelessons.com"/>
			<MT N="contactPhone" V="877-231-8505"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://takelessons.com/uploads/BioPictures/141772_10514_tn.jpg"/>
			<S>My interest in Music was early in my youth. I can remember playing my 45 records and 8 track tapes until they wore out. I have always&amp;nbsp;enjoyed singer/song writer's in genre's like, Rock, R&amp;amp;B, Folk and Jazz. In the early 1990's I began work as Technician for Live Audio Sound Re-inforcement. After a few years, I began apprencticing in Recording Studio's on the East Coast. Studying with Mark Williams, Rick Dior and Tracy Shrader. After, a few years of Apprenctiship I began my own Project...</S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
		<R N="88">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=097c2354-3b7b-4478-8f0d-000500c27f0a</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=097c2354-3b7b-4478-8f0d-000500c27f0a</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=097c2354-3b7b-4478-8f0d-000500c27f0a</UD>
			<T>Active Trainer--How to delete a single workout</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Active Trainer Athlete Tutorial--Delete workouts"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="Delete Workouts Training Calendar"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-02-21"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/35/ddf7/d65fe83229e4c8ec15b5cff776/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="89">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=0ef84587-227f-4d1e-afcc-0035b6444797</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=0ef84587-227f-4d1e-afcc-0035b6444797</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=0ef84587-227f-4d1e-afcc-0035b6444797</UD>
			<T>80 Anthony Chris Canyon Trail</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V=""/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/a5/11ec/a8d9c9e8b7ec4939756e546f39/thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="90">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=09334889-6ec0-47d3-bc57-0054bd4e5d3e</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=09334889-6ec0-47d3-bc57-0054bd4e5d3e</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=09334889-6ec0-47d3-bc57-0054bd4e5d3e</UD>
			<T>73 Behunin Canyon</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V=""/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/a3/55fc/83f9e8ca0bc462e59f1647c9c5/thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="91">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=ba62c1e3-9b6b-45ea-92df-0054d23d81b8</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=ba62c1e3-9b6b-45ea-92df-0054d23d81b8</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=ba62c1e3-9b6b-45ea-92df-0054d23d81b8</UD>
			<T>97 3rd Rap Anthony Down</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V=""/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/04/c9ab/29e49bb09d45c18aa10b1bc0e4/thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="92">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=a7b8d937-30fb-469b-a43d-0055c45ddfd6</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=a7b8d937-30fb-469b-a43d-0055c45ddfd6</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=a7b8d937-30fb-469b-a43d-0055c45ddfd6</UD>
			<T>World Run Day - November 11, 2007 (version #1)</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="International Day for Running is announced as &quot;World Run Day&quot;. Video is an inspirational slideshow of prior year's events to music of Sting's &quot;Brand New Day.&quot; Register early as an individual or small group for event t-shirt and name listing on www.runday."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="World,Run,Day,Charity,Marathon"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2007-10-09"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/ee/dc67/38ac250cc9cdf52884d2fe985d/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="93">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=f9791010-e4d6-43fd-bf0f-005d28205170</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=f9791010-e4d6-43fd-bf0f-005d28205170</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=f9791010-e4d6-43fd-bf0f-005d28205170</UD>
			<T>75745538</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V=""/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/6a/4638/dfea6aa45a35b4d3e5d4abea22/thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="94">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=35c67c40-69e7-40ec-8845-0098b4ee57fb</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=35c67c40-69e7-40ec-8845-0098b4ee57fb</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=35c67c40-69e7-40ec-8845-0098b4ee57fb</UD>
			<T>VID00019</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V=""/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/f2/3704/15fa6d8d5cadf2e28378d35f4b/thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="95">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=3080a1a6-a57b-4e1d-875b-00acc6e423e3</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=3080a1a6-a57b-4e1d-875b-00acc6e423e3</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=3080a1a6-a57b-4e1d-875b-00acc6e423e3</UD>
			<T>ActiveX - Edward Scissorkicks</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="5 rounds:&amp;#0A;400 run&amp;#0A;100 lunges&amp;#0A;50 scissorkicks [1,2,3,4 = 1]&amp;#0A;30 push ups"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Other"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="ActiveX, boot camp"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-02-07"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/69/01cf/ccd23d5ca7745aa32627f3a1f3/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="96">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=23a56578-45d9-4ebb-9716-00b883fe4cca</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=23a56578-45d9-4ebb-9716-00b883fe4cca</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=23a56578-45d9-4ebb-9716-00b883fe4cca</UD>
			<T>PACE TREK 2008</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Paul Staso runs across Montana"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Running"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="running, paul staso, kid fitness, ultra, marathon, montana"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-05-19"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/44/108b/9f12dba723dcfc26a16ee9f14b/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="97">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=9c58f5fa-e577-4fc8-bddd-00c752fd2ffe</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=9c58f5fa-e577-4fc8-bddd-00c752fd2ffe</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=9c58f5fa-e577-4fc8-bddd-00c752fd2ffe</UD>
			<T>Soccer Tip 1</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Coach Marty Schupak &amp;amp; www.SoccerCoachOne.com present another important youth soccer tip for coaches, parents, and players. Visit www.SoccerCoachOne.com for more youth sports tips and to browse through a wide collection of sports instructional DVDs."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Soccer"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="sports, tips, clips, tip, clip, youth, soccer, Marty Schupak, coaching, instruction, shooting, goalie, futbol"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2007-09-18"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/c8/3b33/22aa8671b3fb2a4b71c44f7702/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="98">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=1d222b8b-726a-422c-826a-00fa48a21f85</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=1d222b8b-726a-422c-826a-00fa48a21f85</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=1d222b8b-726a-422c-826a-00fa48a21f85</UD>
			<T>Senior Day @ LUC</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="The end of 4 great years"/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Softball"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="softball, fastpitch, luc"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2007-08-09"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/7b/f6fb/a7a75eaac01ecb86a6ef678ad3/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="99">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=08549300-3d6f-499b-86b4-011f9d681689</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=08549300-3d6f-499b-86b4-011f9d681689</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=08549300-3d6f-499b-86b4-011f9d681689</UD>
			<T>Music on a bike - no heaphones</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="A demo on how to listen to mp3 music and have easy access to your phone while cycling. No headphones."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Cycling"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="BevyTech Gadget Bottle MP3 Phone Road Commute Bike headphone"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-01-10"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/82/ed8b/d50d09365a334228f86c43fa2b/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>
		<R N="100">
			<U>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=d656c5d9-65f1-48f7-8400-015d3d47d23d</U>
			<UE>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=d656c5d9-65f1-48f7-8400-015d3d47d23d</UE>
			<UD>http://www.active.com/video/play.htm?id=d656c5d9-65f1-48f7-8400-015d3d47d23d</UD>
			<T>Federer vs. Garcia-Lopez - Pac-Life 08</T>
			<RK>10</RK>
			<CRAWLDATE> 21 May 2008</CRAWLDATE>
			<MT N="keywords" V=""/>
			<MT N="Generator" V=""/>
			<MT N="UpdateDateTime" V="3/3/2008 4:26:06 PM"/>
			<MT N="description" V="Roger Federer advances to Round 2 of the 2008 Pacific Life Open after defeating Guillermo Garcia-Lopez 6-3, 6-2. For more, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.active.com/tennis/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Active.com/tennis&lt;/a&gt;."/>
			<MT N="category" V="Videos &amp; Photos"/>
			<MT N="channel" V="Tennis"/>
			<MT N="tags" V="tennis"/>
			<MT N="mediaType" V="Video"/>
			<MT N="startDate" V="2008-03-17"/>
			<MT N="photoURL" V="http://media.jumpcut.com/media/dyn/d1/d901/ddaffb236f7011cefe15b26223/movie_thumb120x90.jpg"/>
			<S> </S>
			<LANG>en</LANG>
			<HAS>
				<L/>
				<C SZ="49k" CID="t6DrjZ4QeKcJ" ENC="ISO-8859-1"/>
			</HAS>
		</R>	
	</RES>
</GSP>